Oh, that was a good one.
You hear these drops in the background?
Some of them are fake, some of them are not.
All these drops you've heard so far in this music...
I've been doing it manually.
I'm kidding.
It wasn't me.
I did do the ones just before.
You can probably tell the difference.
Here comes one of mine.
Oh, I nailed it.
Oh, so good.
What's up, people?
Hive is here.
Happy birthday, Hive.
Good to have you.
Roy, thank you so much for resubscribing.
I love that you can put a message on it, too.
I feel like people are loving that new gif.
It's so good.
Ludwig, thanks for resubscribing as well.
What's up, everybody, huh?
Too good to be real.
Oliver, did you know that it's the one-year anniversary since you made the Discord public?
Wait, is that really?
Is that true?
No way.
Has it already been a year?
That's crazy.
No way.
Already?
Wow.
Time flies, huh?
We're all getting older.
Did you check the VOD from last time?
I sure did, you jury.
Not only that, I have... I watched it like ten times in a row, and I think I understood what happened.
And I will not fall for that shit again.
Oh my god, Ludwig, gifting a bunch of subs.
Thank you so much.
Holy shit.
You know what's funny here?
Half-loaf was one of the few that got that sub just now from Ludwig, and the half-loaf has also been gifting subs.
It all comes together.
It's all full circle.
Thank you, man.
I really appreciate it.
Study the ways of the enemies.
Okay, listen, this is what I think happened.
So I watched that clip again and again.
That guy switched places with me, and he did it so fast.
That the shots that I shot killed myself.
And they killed myself because those shots were dealing damage to me.
Because I had that spell.
I forget the name of it now.
But the plus damage spell.
Don't tell me if it's true or not.
But I think that's pretty much what happened, and I'm like 99% sure.
Netrack!
Hey, man.
Welcome.
I haven't seen your name before.
You don't have to say anything, by the way.
I just appreciate it.
Thank you.
We need more crazy Oliver emotes?
Dude, tell me which ones to make and I'll put them in.
We have a bunch of slots for emotes.
We can have so many more.
The more subscribers we have, the more emote slots.
And right now there's a lot of slots available so we can put in anything.
A demon emote would be nice.
Yes, we should do something like that.
We need a bad so demon face.
Fuck yeah, let's do it.
A lot of what?
You know, a bunch of slots, a bunch of...
God, you know what I mean.
Damn it.
Dude.
I'm in a really good mood today.
I was really tired this morning for some reason.
I rolled out of bed straight to work.
And I was just sitting there like a zombie.
You know, but nothing fills you up with more energy than knowing you're going to be playing games.
It's the truth.
Albin et al.
Oh, I love your name.
Reference to papers, right?
Unless that's just a pure coincidence.
Thank you for subscribing.
Albin et al.
I actually never knew how to say that correctly.
It al.
I think it's it al.
As long as we don't have any lemon stealing whores, we're fine.
I know that reference.
I know all the references.
You cannot stop me.
How about a second dancing hymn is that start the opposite direction than the current one?
You know what?
That sounds funny as hell.
It's happening.
Thank you.
That will happen next stream.
I'm putting that in.
That's a great one.
I'm going to make a bunch.
If you go to Discord in the channel related channel, that sounds a little bit funny to say, but if you go there and suggest these things, it would be easier for me to look back at it when I have to actually make them.
I'd love one where you're wearing a black fold yourself.
Yeah, maybe.
I can I can maybe cook something up like that.
Yeah, and the rest.
Exactly.
It means I'm the rest.
I mean, I just didn't know how to pronounce it, basically is what I meant.
Do you have seven TV emotes enabled on your channel?
I am not sure, Ducky Bird.
Maybe someone can test that right now.
I do have an extension that I installed at some point.
I have better Twitch TV extension installed on Chrome right now.
And I and I think is that the one you know, maybe that's not the same thing.
I don't think I do, but maybe I can look into that seven TV.
Seven TV.
What a weird name.
It's the successor to better Twitch.
Oh.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I was told to put better Twitch on.
Basically the same, but more emotes.
Oh, OK.
Cool.
For me, it doesn't show up, Frank.
When I look at chat, I can't see it.
I see you wrote, let's test clap.
I didn't see an emote.
I'm assuming clap is an emote.
So I guess I need to.
So it's only for the people who have it installed.
I can see it right.
Everyone needs to have it.
So me installing it won't do anything for you, right?
Oh, and the screen shows up.
Oh, that's probably because chat goes through stream elements.
Ah, OK, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I see that actually on the preview.
OK.
Yep.
I'm assuming stream elements has all the emotes that you can have.
OK, Sip Bang Crash.
Good to see you again.
Thank you for cheering.
I'm still not quite sure how that works, but I really appreciate it.
A hundred bits.
Not sure what that means.
I think someone told me once, but I'm not sure.
Thank you.
Just cheering me on, I guess.
I'm cheering myself on.
I'm feeling confident today.
Last time I had a couple good runs, you know, like they weren't long runs, but I had some crazy perks like it was going swell until I came in and fucked it up.
You know, the game gave me every opportunity to become successful.
And I just fucked it up.
But I learned a bunch of lessons in the process.
So I will take those lessons to heart and hopefully improve and we shall get far along today.
I want to fill out more of the map.
I know there are areas on the map that I haven't filled out yet that I want to fill out.
And also more secrets to find, right?
But I'm also prepared to just die repeatedly.
It can happen.
People have been have been saying noitred that when you die noiter, you get noitred.
I like that.
I think it's quite fitting.
OK.
I will close you guys down.
And hopefully we're not going to get a scary sound now.
When I click this button.
Dammit.
Game crashed.
It's because of this special K.
But it only seems to do it in the beginning, so.
I don't know.
I don't know why that is.
Why is it working after that?
That's so weird.
OK.
I don't think I was in the middle of a run.
I'm pretty sure I died again and then I had to, you know.
Start over.
Yeah, here I am.
Here I am.
OK, hold on, let's recap.
What I did last time, I filled this out.
Magical temple.
I'm not actually sure that's the name of it.
I may have remembered wrong when I wrote that, but we filled in.
Oh, hold on, you can't see what I'm writing, of course.
We filled in this.
And the orb room here.
But I know that there's something here as well.
I forgot the name of it or what exactly it is, but I'm going to fill it out.
Also want to fill this out today as much as I can.
I also added just a tiny cosmetic changes on my own since last time, just to make the map look nice.
I want to keep it sort of black and whiteish with a couple of colors here and there.
You know, I don't want to colorize it, per se.
Demon eye.
Pahisilma, I think I wrote that wrong, by the way.
This should be remove that.
I think it was like that.
Yeah, I don't know what it means.
I kind of want to just Google translate some of these Finnish names, you know, just because it could be fun.
OK, I think he means spider, right?
Hurta, I think it means dog, but I'm not sure.
All right, back to the game.
Let's see.
All right, guys, see you on the other side.
Hmm.
A new day, a new run.
We have bombs at our disposal.
We have good mental fortitude at our disposal as well.
What can go wrong?
There is something very comforting about being in the hemisphere.
You know, it's like it's like home.
It's like coming home.
Dying is not dying, dying is just coming home.
That's how you should see it.
That's how I see it.
Hurta is a little aggressive today, and he's in a very annoying spot.
How am I going to get you out of there?
OK, he's going to get out of there himself.
There we go.
And there's a wand immediately.
That's good.
Very good.
Toxic sludge.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I have water.
Perfect.
Good thing we checked that.
That guy was a little out of control.
Hey, that's a good start.
Flammoxium.
Don't really care for that.
There's got to be a use for flammoxium.
You know, I imagine there's a use for most things in this game, but it's not obvious at first sight.
So while I may not experiment with flammoxium right now, it is something I intend to do down the road.
Among so many other things in this game, by the way.
You know, this game is massive.
And I am addicted.
I have to say, I really am bitten.
Smitten is the word, I think, by this game.
Why is everything on fire?
Sometimes I feel like a detective coming into these places, you know.
And I have this crime scene here.
I have to deduce what the hell happened.
I think a bomb man threw some bombs, hit some fireworks and something happened after that spread from there.
Protected by a cart.
Sir, hand over your monies.
Kind of want to go in the dark cave.
But I'm also scared of the worm.
If I find a sick wand here, something with a good amount of damage, like I don't want to say saw blades, but disc projectiles, then I may actually do it because that does a decent amount of damage.
If I find something like that, I will go grab a worm.
Just so we can get that night vision.
You can see I'm doing this systematically now.
I go the highest level I can to each direction, and then I go the next highest level and keep going.
Well, I guess it wasn't quite perfect, but I'm trying, OK?
I'm trying to keep it systematic here.
Man, if it wasn't for the map lighting up wherever you go, I would be so incredibly lost in this game at all times.
I mean, I already am, but times a thousand, OK?
I'm so grateful for that.
Would have been impossible without it.
What's that?
Oh, it's a...
Wow, it's broken.
Huh, weird.
A wheel fell off.
Oh, oh, OK, OK, OK, those guys are so scary.
Got him.
Three shots.
Oh, hold on, that's actually one.
Let me check that.
Puff of air, I want to call it puff of air.
Burst of air.
Sure.
Also, burst of air if I put that on fire.
Right, that's actually amazing.
I guess you you add oxygen, right, which fuels the flame.
I wonder what this does to other things.
Like, look at that, you can totally fan the flame.
It's like a smithy, you know.
How much damage does this do?
Six damage is pretty good.
Pretty good.
Wait, what?
Did that thing just bounce?
Oh, you see that?
I just bounced the gold up into me.
Oh, my God, it bounces things a lot.
Or I guess I should say knockback is really what that is.
I didn't realize until now that knockback could actually come in handy.
Right?
Also, I just realized, am I triggering a trap right here?
I see this over here.
Uh oh, did I just fuck up?
Hold on.
Oh, yeah, this is totally, it's totally a trap.
Is that a saw blade?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I got to destroy that.
Let me do this.
Oh, good.
Can I even...
Ah, that's decent.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Punch it upward and then shoot it.
Okay, whatever.
Didn't quite work.
But here's what I'm going to do.
Oh, okay, so that symbol is not a saw blade.
It's a gas symbol, I guess.
Huh.
All right.
It totally looked like a saw blade.
Well, that went well.
I'm looking at this thinking it's good because of the one.
Look, .07, .83.
It's not bad.
Small spread, oh, it only has two slots, though.
That's the thing.
Maybe I don't want it.
Do I want it?
Otherwise, empty egg, that casts a spell.
No, don't take it yet, but I will take it on my way out.
Because I want to use these two bombs that I have, basically.
That's the plan.
Burst of air.
Wait a minute, this looks like a worm, doesn't it?
Do we have a worm on the loose?
No, wait, that would show something here, I think.
Bro, the burst of air is neat.
I am really starting to take a liking to this.
I've been sleeping on it, I think.
I need to try this on all kinds of things.
What was that sound?
It came from over here.
Look how much it punches him.
Or pushes him around.
I heard like a... sound.
Somewhere.
Also, my systematic exploration technique here is sort of not working anymore.
Invisiblium.
Very nice.
Another thing I want to do more is to use my potions.
So if I find berserkium in a potion, I should start using it all the time.
You know, just drink it here and there.
Whenever I'm about to get into a fight, just chuck that shit.
Like right here.
Let's just put this on.
Oh wait, no, we have to douse ourselves with that, never mind.
How?
You absolute fucker.
I thought I was invisible.
I do not like that.
The fact that I can push around the gold is actually really nice.
That's a worm.
What?
It went to here and went back?
Or did it spawn there and keep... Oh, I'm so confused.
I should be scared, actually.
Because the gods could get angry.
This is not a good situation.
What should I call that worm on the loose?
Something elusive.
Louise.
Is the name of that worm.
Kind of wanted to call it a very specific name of a girl that got away, just because elusive.
But I don't want to do that.
I don't want to say that name.
So for all intents and purposes, that name is now Louise.
Change that.
We have our...
My dude is vibrating.
Stop it.
I wonder why that worm went.
It went like for a little joyride here and then out again.
Look.
Ah, I see you.
This is my chance.
We got to kill that immediately.
It's happening.
Hold on.
I should empty my...
I see a nice little spot here.
Check this out.
I'm going to put this in here.
So I can grab it again later if I need to.
Look how much there is.
It's wild.
And now, we're going to grab that blood.
What was that sound?
Wait, what's happening?
Huh?
Wait, what's this?
Break it apart.
Okay, whatever.
Fill it up.
Oh wait, I thought that was way more blood.
Am I tripping?
Well, I don't need more than that anyway.
It's fine.
Shit, I thought I could collect like half a bottle at least.
Dammit.
Okay, so there's two hearts in there.
That's fantastic.
And I can even get the one on top of the mountain.
Because I have this one.
This is a good start.
That's 175 HP guaranteed.
Hell yeah!
I'm going to go there right now.
Also, I'm glad to take out that worm anyway.
Because it could have angered the gods later on.
That was the egg.
Man, everything is dissolved here.
What's that?
Teleportation.
Ooh, that's bad.
Don't get in there.
Oh, I'm stuck!
How did I get myself into this?
Ah, come on!
I can't.
How the...
Hold on, I'm actually stuck.
I can't get out.
Ah, there we go.
Nice.
I was just about to use my firebolt to carve my way out.
But I was afraid of damaging myself with it, you know.
Bro,
why does the burst of air do 14 damage?
So this does 6 damage.
So if I hit him twice, it's 12.
How does that get to 14?
That confuses me.
This is also a great opportunity to fill out the map over here.
But I have a very limited amount of blood, so...
I just have to work from memory right after I see it.
Basically what I need to see is if it's the same layout as last time or not.
Because if it's not the same, then I'm just going to put in like a blank square.
Pheromone.
Oh, oh no no no no.
In fact, those guys, I'm just going to take them out with a firebolt.
I don't have patience to handle the other thing.
Thank you.
Frogs.
Blow them up.
What's that?
Based on the color, I think this is...
Concentrated mana.
Yeah!
Getting the ropes of this.
Oh!
Amazing!
Oh shit.
Oh, I gotta be careful with the burst of air, actually, if you're near fire, obviously.
It could kill you.
Give me that.
Oh my god!
Are you guys seeing this?
That's insane!
Two hearts right next to each other like that.
Damn.
I have been blessed this day.
Doing!
What else we got here?
A bunch of oil.
Someone put oil there and then put up a barrier to contain it.
So much work for something that doesn't make any sense.
That guy's chopping up his friends because he's a psycho.
Come on, man.
Don't be like that.
He did it.
Man, the firebolt is doing some damage.
My bro, come on.
Oh, look at those guys.
Holy shit, there's a whole gang of very scary enemies there.
Yeah, we got it, we got it, we got it.
Oh god.
Die, please.
Jesus.
One more shot.
Got him.
So much gold I'm missing here, but I'm not taking the chance.
I am playing this safe.
Kind of need to find more water too.
I could go...
So there's this dude right here.
What is the best way to deal with him?
Water, right?
Ah!
He's just waiting.
I don't like that.
Let me go up instead first.
Uh-oh.
Got him.
That was sweet.
Oh, that was nice.
Firebolt is incredible.
Like early on, the damage from it is wildly good.
He's just standing there menacingly, look.
Can I hit him with a fireball if I arc it perfectly?
Oh, that was too much.
Nah, I don't trust him.
We're gonna go somewhere else.
He's gonna drop down.
Those guys have a lot of HP.
Come on, man.
Oh, what if I burst of air on him?
I can fan the flames on him.
Yo, that's effective, I think.
Look at that!
Weirdly, he takes damage from fire, so that's kind of weird.
Oh god, oh god.
Maybe not that much.
There's some water for you.
Now he's sort of down there.
That's for you, man.
I'm actually out of water.
Ah, nice, he died in the water down here.
What is that?
A chili egg?
Ah, no, thanks.
There's gotta be a... See, that thing right there?
There's a use for it somewhere, for sure.
And I want to find out what it is.
So when I find a spot that could be a candidate for any of these things in the game, so so far a lot of the puzzles, or like secrets you could even say, depend on you bringing a certain item to a certain spot and dropping it.
Right?
A.K.A.
bringing a tablet up above.
Your curiosity is rewarded.
Or dropping some water into a container, right?
And something happens.
Or bringing the broken wand to the anvil.
Stuff like that.
Okay, we're here.
Ah, let's see.
How do we do this the best way?
So the problem is, I don't have teleport wand right now.
Hmm.
But we can probably make it in time.
Okay, I'm going to drink this.
Here we go.
Oh, wait, let me stand here first.
Go.
Oh, whoa, whoa, that's that's not good.
That's not good.
So only six seconds.
No, I can't make it.
I can't make it.
No, no, no.
We need to.
Oh, shit.
You know what I should have done?
I should have drained this.
Before I did that.
God damn it, I wasted my opportunity.
I could probably find just a droplet more of that worm blood if I go back to where he died.
And try it again.
Yeah, let me just keep exploring and we're going to go back to the worm at some point.
See if we can't extract just a tiny bit more of that blood.
Someone down there?
Who's down there?
Let me actually get rid of that.
There we go.
Copper.
This is so far a good start, though.
We found two hearts right next to each other.
We have decent wants.
This is good.
Oh, look at that.
A big ass guy hiding there.
Let's go kill him.
In fact, you know what?
Every time I see a bunch of toxic sludge, it's basically a...
Oh, that's all water.
Because I can turn it into water and then I can pick it up after.
That's how I should be seeing these pools.
Potential water to get.
Come on, man, mix.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
I was standing into something there.
Thank you.
Fireball time.
Oh, yeah.
That gold is not happening.
Unfortunately.
Careful.
Swamp.
This is some very dirty water I have right here.
Hey, miss.
Man, the worm has been at work here.
Louise.
Jeez, Louise.
What have you done?
Oh, I thought it was a guy who was alive.
400 gold?
Not bad.
Now, where did that worm die?
Somewhere over here, I think.
It was close to a portal.
Look at the stack.
There we go.
Blow them.
Out of the way.
Wait, where was that worm?
I think I may have passed it.
That's OK.
Let's keep exploring.
I didn't even see you there.
You bastard.
I was looking somewhere completely else on my screen.
Like I was trying to see if there was something hiding in here.
Haha.
That guy got me good.
Stupid him.
I guess I am on his home turf.
I kind of want to make a hole here.
Oh, come on.
Really?
Shit.
I'm not going to waste another shot.
Like Louise has been at work here.
Oh, that's gold.
Dude, that was crazy last time.
We were in the coal pits and I don't know exactly what happened, but suddenly there was gold everywhere in the level.
And it was just crazy.
I was so rich and then I died.
It was so unfortunate.
The potential in that was off the charts.
Kind of hope that happens again.
I may have just gotten lucky.
I wonder if there are some of these things that happen in the game that only happen after a certain amount of time you've been playing.
Or amount of deaths you have, you know?
So that's... Oh, that's my Invisibilium.
That means the worm is here.
Okay, so what's going in the right direction?
Oh, here it is.
Here it is.
Can I grab a bit more?
Maybe.
I think I just did.
I think I just picked up some more.
Don't accidentally go in the portal.
What if I shoot these corpses?
Will they produce blood?
I think so, actually.
They're dripping, look!
Yeah!
Yay!
Hold on.
Kick it!
I need a cleaver.
Oh, yeah, look at all that blood.
16% worm blood now.
That's not bad!
Eh?
Now we have a shot at trying that again.
I need more water as well, so look at this.
We mix...
and then we grab.
The old mixing grab.
MNG.
That filling up with...
Huh?
How did that not fill up with more water?
That's crazy.
Nah, I don't want to go that way.
So we've reached the end on the right side.
Now it's time to go back to the cave.
The watery cave.
What is happening down here?
There's nothing there, right?
Doesn't... Oh, wait, you know what?
We can take some blood.
It works just as well as fire.
I mean, water, not fire.
And it gives us crit.
Ooh.
Oh, no.
Okay, okay, thank God.
It's weird how you can get into these situations where you're stuck.
Whoa, look at all the blood!
That's a tube of blood right there.
I.V.
Fill up my water bottle.
Okay, let's go.
I need to go to the foot of the cave and see if I can use my bomb to clear it out.
Even if I had infinite night vision right now, I still wouldn't be able to go through.
There's too much water.
I can't hold my breath for that long.
Here's someone throwing.
Wait, where was that guy?
That's the dead end there.
I need to go up and this way, sort of.
58 HP.
I haven't even made it to collapsed mines yet.
I go here.
Let me go this way.
Here we go.
Unexplored territory.
This almost looks too good to be true.
This is the perfect spot.
Drain that shit.
Oh, I didn't make it all the way here.
I kind of want to open up this as well.
Let's use... hmm.
How do I get in here?
That's the question.
Ah man, the fireball is going to disappear in the water.
So I can't really dig with that.
Aha!
But wait.
If I'm shrewd enough...
This is going to be a little tricky.
I was going to say, use burst of air, but that also damages.
So that's not a good idea here, but...
I will be taking this.
Please don't randomly explode after a bunch of kicking.
I don't think it will, because there's no damage numbers showing up on it when I kick it.
So it may actually be completely fine.
Come on.
Come on now.
Heh heh.
Yep, yep.
It's all bloody.
Heh heh.
Yes!
Oh god.
I'm getting a little scared.
Ah, don't drown now, please.
Ah, come on.
This is difficult, man.
Hey!
There we go, there we go.
Yes!
Yes, come on.
A little further.
Why do you kick it straight upwards, you idiot?
No!
Yes.
Come on.
Yes!
There it is!
Here we go!
I'm so smart!
God damn!
Look at that!
That feels good, man.
But wait, it's only gonna... Oh, okay.
I thought it was going further down.
But maybe that's enough.
Oh, that's annoying.
Burst of air doesn't go far on the water.
Maybe he deserves to be left alive.
Oh, but he can't hit me either.
There we go.
Beautiful.
Let me see here.
I can actually...
Okay, I think I'm just gonna try it, guys.
I could actually grab that too.
No, that's too much work.
How should I get it up here, right?
That's gonna be hell.
What I'm gonna do...
is I'm gonna consume this and swim from below.
Okay, you ready?
Here we go!
No way, no way, no way, no way.
We can't make that.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not happening.
Oh, but look at this.
It's happening.
60 seconds of vision, this is perfect.
Nice!
Oh, but wait, that's...
that looks different.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, is that not a...
Hold on.
Oh, wait, I'm going the wrong way, I think.
How do I get down there?
Oh, I have to swim from the other side.
Wait a minute.
Guys, that is a...
that's not a heart.
I mean, it is a heart, but this is the healing.
This is not a increased max health.
Right?
Pulsating like that.
And it doesn't say plus.
The hell?
So I can actually heal there.
That's crazy.
Okay, let's keep that in mind.
Also, I think I may have explored everything down here.
Where the hell are the collapsed mines?
Now I'm thinking, maybe it's not always here.
You know?
Okay, I think it's time to go through anyway.
Here we go.
Let's see what we got.
I like the black hole.
What's this?
Faster Wands.
All Wands you're currently carrying gain a bonus of their Castellan reload time.
Huh.
Loot Commutation.
Projectile Eater.
Small sector behind of you disappear.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
But that I know about.
Plasma Cutter, my beloved.
Yes!
I'm taking that, and I'm taking...
No, I don't want that.
I already have three.
Let's go with...
Let's go with the Toilet Visit.
Hold on, I need to piss real bad.
Be right back.
And I'm back.
Dude, it is raining outside.
Like, here where I live.
It's raining so much, I had to close my window.
Which was barely open because water was spraying in...
Damn.
Okay.
What's...
Let's see here, what did I have?
I have that.
I have...
Luminous Drill with...
What is this one again?
This is the delayed, right?
Delayed Spellcast.
Here's the thing though.
I want to use at least 200 monies on Reroll.
So that means I have...
What is that?
277 left.
Yeah.
Unless I get shitty Rerolls.
I kind of want...
Things are exploding somewhere.
That's fine.
Luminous Drill with Timer.
You know, Rain Cloud could be really nice.
Delayed Spell...
I'm just going to buy...
Give me this one.
Okay.
Let's re-roll these.
I don't like any of these.
Especially not the Lukey mutation.
Is that what I think it is?
No, okay.
Gas is near you, ignite.
What's this?
Revenge Rats.
When you take damage, there's a chance that a helpful rat minion is summoned.
No!
Liquids freeze in your presence.
Dude, I hate all of these.
I'm not taking them.
I'm coming back for a re-roll.
Dammit!
Okay.
That's fine.
So, but now look, I can do digging.
I can dig.
Oh, but wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's fine, that's fine.
Definitely want to dig.
That's not bad.
Let's just try some more.
Just to see which one is the best.
Wait a minute.
Okay, this one is definitely better.
Oh yeah, that's super good, that's super good.
This one is not gonna...
Oh!
It's not bad!
It's just a very slow recharge, right?
Nope, that's definitely the best for that.
It has been determined.
Now, my damage wand.
It may just be spark bolts, really.
What about the second one?
Yo, that's not bad at all!
In fact, that's really good.
Just a single spark bolt.
But maybe if we put burst of air, maybe it's better.
That could be damage, right?
But then again, spark bolt is more reliable, I think.
Because burst of air also pushes things around.
That makes me a little bit scared.
Then on this one, let's put...
Luminous...
Hold on.
Luminous drill with timer.
It actually reduces castellae by a significant amount.
Like, holy shit!
Minus 0.6?
So wait, wait, does that mean...
What does that mean?
Hold on.
This adds 0.05 castellae.
So...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I see, I see, I see.
Dude.
Dude, how is this wand not insane?
Ah, mana charge is very slow, but...
There's not that much mana anyway, so this is actually acceptable.
That is an acceptable damage wand.
Now this wand is limited by recharge right now.
That's the limiting factor.
So you know what?
I think I'm just gonna ring cloud it.
Just some utility there.
You know?
Maybe on this one instead.
And then on the last one...
I mean, we could put black hole, but here's the thing.
Kind of want to keep black hole up here.
No.
Let me use it here.
Oh, no more mana.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I can't use it at all.
Okay, never mind then.
Gotcha.
That was the best for that.
And this one is just gonna stay empty, I think.
1.07, oh, put it on here then.
Okay.
Let's move on.
Ah, I'm gonna heal.
I'm gonna heal.
Better safe than sorry.
And did you look at the heart?
It's the same heart we saw in the dark cave.
So it's confirmed.
That one is actually a heal.
It's not a health increase.
Okay, hold on.
Let's be scientific.
Where exactly does this trigger now?
Let's look really carefully.
If I go straight up from the left side.
Okay, so it's right here.
Oh, let's not get hit by those.
So it's like, right here, right?
So if you go above this, on this side, you're like, that's how you trigger the collapse.
Okay, cold pits.
The air in the back of your neck stands up.
I think that means there are ghosts on the enemies.
But I'm not sure what that actually means, you know?
Like, okay, they're there, so what?
Aha!
Oh, wait, shit.
You want to come over here?
Damn, boy.
Now that's a wand right there.
I'll be taking that, thank you.
That's great, thank you very much.
All I need now is explosion immunity.
And I'm set, boy.
Don't want to shoot it, because above and below...
Don't want to do that.
Invisiblium!
Hey, hey, hey!
Uh-oh.
Man has HP.
Are you stuck?
Look at all that slime.
Oh, my goodness.
Okay, this wand is worse than I thought.
Like, it shoots fast, but my god, is the damage terrible.
I mean, I know what I was getting into, you know?
It's just a spark bolt.
But still, I... I don't know, I expected more.
That's burning.
I can get in here.
Let's be careful around this.
Ahh!
Oh, wait, we're fine, we're fine.
Pick it up, pick it up, pick it up, pick it up.
Oh, don't drink it, don't drink it, it makes me sick.
Boom!
Was not ready for him.
Dude, actually having a plasma cutter right now is game-changing.
So early on, having this?
Wow.
Okay.
See, wand there?
No problem.
One second recharge, that's a lot.
Spells per cast six.
Heavy spread, triple scatter on digging bolts?
I am just dying to know what that looks like.
I'm sorry, but I need to see this.
Okay, that's not as exciting as I thought it would be.
Never mind.
Yikes!
At least that guy caught fire.
Oh, there's pixels of...
Get it out of here.
Wait, does blood immediately remove fire?
Because water turns it into a rock, right?
Molten gold?
It melted the gold, it's molten.
Can I cool that down?
Yo, what?
Wait a minute.
Uh, I don't know.
Mix it.
Why don't I have any...
Oh, shit.
It does not cool down in blood, it seems.
Yo, that's a wand, what the hell?
Bloodlust, my beloved!
And saw blade orbit, oh man!
I thought I was out and then you pulled me back in!
Well, I gotta go with it.
I gotta do it, man!
Goddamn!
In fact, let me see the stats on this.
Ah, it's shuffled, never mind, it sucks.
Hold on, hold on.
Before I go that way.
Nah, nah, go that way first.
I will explore all of this.
Look how much HP I have.
But, let's follow rule 13.
Do not get overconfident.
That is the number one killer.
And dude, I can...
I can go anywhere I want!
The plasma cutter is... best in slot.
Like, here?
No problem.
Just, uh...
Actually, I don't want to dig straight down because that scares me.
But, hold on, the plasma cutter actually removes gold, right?
Like, the gold just disappears.
So, that's actually kind of sad.
Nice.
I am so afraid of this cutter.
Look at these fools!
Haha!
Now they know how it feels.
I felt... Oh wait, did I also dissipate the gold they spawned?
Oh man!
I think I did.
Where should I... I'm gonna go down here.
No!
Okay, nice.
I was quick to react.
Oh, that's a bunch of lava.
It's a... Hold on a second.
Lava and gold.
Molten lava.
Makes sense, I guess.
See?
You can put out fires with spells.
Portal.
And... What's happening over there?
Okay, nothing.
Okay, that does not change toxic sludge.
So, that's the disadvantage of not having water.
What if I drink blood?
Okay, it doesn't do much.
I will get rid of this and get water instead.
That's just so much better.
Don't put it there.
Shit.
Put it... What is this?
Empty it over here.
Let's grab this water.
Nice!
We are back, baby.
Back to removing toxic sludge.
The nastiest of them all.
Oh!
Wow, this guy has HP.
Oh, wait, it's...
Oh, he throws those things.
Got him.
Very cool.
Let's get up here.
Can't... Oh, hello!
Nice!
He opened up the door for me.
I appreciate it.
Not that I needed it.
I can open my own damn doors.
Okay.
So, I remember where I was here.
I'm gonna go left now.
Something below us.
What happens if I use this on coal?
It's not gonna set it on fire, right?
No, it is not.
Oh, that guy's gonna die from lava.
Very nice.
I hate stray lava.
Nice.
Thank you!
I have a feeling this guy's gonna...
Kill me.
No, never mind.
That was a good kick.
I think I should be careful around those.
Sweet gold!
What is that?
Ah!
Very nice!
Love that!
This is great so far, man.
There's a little room up there.
Kinda wanna get in.
Let's do it.
Damn it.
I'm so scared of this thing.
This is what ended one of my bigger runs last time.
Dying to my own plasma cutter.
And it ain't the first time either.
I can fill up on water here.
Ah, nice.
Wait, where'd he go?
Watch this.
Oh!
Hello!
Snog up on me there.
I wanted to kill that guy with the rock.
Let's check this out.
Fuck!
I defaulted to this wand to cast this.
Fuck me.
Old habits die hard.
Please not like this.
Come on, man.
Pull yourself together.
Don't do this to yourself.
Please, you're throwing such a good thing away right now.
Oh, I think I lost like 70 HP there.
Something like that.
It was bad.
It was a lot.
It happens though.
Don't do that.
Oh, actually.
Isn't that one sort of sick on its own right now?
Oh!
I forgot about the sawblades.
Yeah, let's...
no.
Don't, don't, don't.
Yeah, the sawblades scare the living crap out of me as well.
Oh, nice.
The game hurt my plea.
I was like, ah, take this heart.
You deserve it.
You little bugger, you.
And I said, okay.
You see that dodge?
That was pro.
I kind of want to empty this, of course.
No, I don't.
Ah, hold on.
Oh, I almost did it again.
Okay, I need to really fix this.
This cannot be in the second.
In fact, I'm scared just having this around.
Don't use two.
Don't.
For fuck's sake.
I need to calm down for a bit.
What is that?
The kicking, I don't quite understand.
Oh, no.
It's fine.
Sometimes it doesn't go in the direction I want it to.
Like, see, that's good.
What am I not getting here?
Like, when you stand on top of it, it sort of...
shoots it in the direction you're facing.
Wait a minute.
Can I actually just...
Let me test something.
I'm standing on top of it.
I face right.
It goes right.
What if I stand on top of it?
I face left.
Wait, can I aim?
Hold on.
What if I go...
down?
Oh, no.
Okay, no one.
Or...
Wait a minute.
Am I finally understanding this?
I think I understand how this works now.
I can't believe I didn't...
try that.
Like, 50 hours ago.
God damn it.
I always thought, oh, it's just in the...
you know, sort of direction your character's facing.
Oh, no.
This is the problem with this wand.
It's low on mana now, and I have to play defensive.
That's fine.
I have some crazy wands in the works right now.
All I need is explosion immunity, electricity immunity, and damage immunity.
And then I'm good.
Then I can do it.
You know?
That's all I need.
That's all I ask for.
Can I have it?
Game?
Hook me up.
Okay.
What's happening here?
That's mysterious.
Nice.
That wasn't too bad.
Vine!
Oh!
Fungal Caverns!
That's right.
The air feels extremely humid.
So that basically means that you retain wet stain for longer, right?
Oh, man.
I'm not going to kill that guy.
This is going to be a little bit of a problem.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
Oh, we're fine.
We're fine.
Are we fine?
Maybe I don't go in there.
Maybe I don't go in the Fungal Caverns.
Oh, God.
His reach.
Jesus.
Oh, you know what?
No.
I'm not going to risk the sawblades.
Even though they probably won't hurt me, I just...
I don't trust it.
I am so deathly afraid of it.
Okay, hold on.
So, Fungal Caverns.
Let's see how this connects.
It's like...
It's sort of...
It's just an extension of it, it seems like.
So...
Hold on.
Let's do that.
Coal pits.
So I guess it's like...
Maybe that size.
Let's say it's sort of...
I don't know exactly how big it is.
Let's remove this part.
Ah, damn it.
That was a bit too much.
Like this.
All the way down.
Actually, maybe I don't remove that line, you know?
Maybe I just sort of...
Do it like this, so that it's indicated there's...
A new place in there like that.
You know?
And then...
We're gonna go with...
Fungal...
Cavern.
Okay.
And it seems like it's always to the west as well.
Cool.
I'm not gonna go in there.
Because that place has a tendency to fuck me up.
Let's put that on our to-do list later in this run.
Go back there and explore that place.
And map it out properly.
Because I'm not sure I ever really explored that place to its fullest, you know?
I always ended up dying or retreating.
Because of crazy stuff happening.
Also, four is digging.
Four is digging.
Is that just gonna lead straight into...
What's down here?
Now this.
Just a tit.
Bit of water.
And mix.
Look at it.
Cool.
Whoa!
Jesus!
Alright, I'm not gonna mess with that guy.
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope.
In fact, maybe I don't even go...
Yeah, we're out.
Don't go that way.
We're coming back later.
I came to the wrong neighborhood there, obviously.
What's in here?
This guy really wants a piece of me?
I'll let him have it.
Whoa!
Ah!
Oh, you are not dead.
I thought you had died.
Oh, that's a mess.
Okay, it was just a small cavern.
Gotcha.
What is going on there?
Did a shotgun man died on there or is he alive?
No, he's definitely dead and somehow stuck in that.
That's weird.
Poison arc.
I wonder...
Okay.
Never mind.
Nope, don't want it.
I do want some more water though, thanks.
Always keep your water bottle filled.
As much as possible.
Ooh!
A shiny orb.
What happens if I hit it with the thing?
It just gets obliterated.
Okay.
As expected.
But now we know.
Can I still pick it up?
Oh no, I'm stuck again.
What is it with me getting stuck today?
Ah, just get rid of it.
I don't like the shiny orb.
It explodes.
Abnormally large amounts of lava came out of that guy.
Wait.
Shit.
Oh!
Oh, no you don't.
I don't know what that's going to do to me, I'm scared.
Hello?
Yeah.
Oh no.
Yeah, he hits me with that shit.
Oh, that's annoying.
That is really annoying.
I don't even want to deal with him.
In fact, I'm deathly afraid of those guys after what happened last time.
Okay.
There's something up there.
Is it just coal?
Oh!
It is.
Okay.
68 HP?
What is that?
Looks like a chess piece.
Don't you even think about it.
This shit's going to burn for a while.
And in fact, can I...
I thought maybe I could dissolve the...
Oh, I can.
Did I just dissolve the fire with my plasma cutter?
Oh, that was close.
Hold on, I need to recharge.
There we go.
Yeah!
And the wand!
Oh, here comes the gang.
Where are you going?
Come back here.
There's a wand up here.
Aha!
Mix that up.
Luminous drill.
How's the wand though?
Not great.
Don't want it.
I reject.
Look at all this coal.
I shouldn't be surprised.
The coal mines.
No, coal pits is the name.
The tiniest pixel prevented me from entering.
Another wand.
Oh, wait.
I thought that was gold.
But I guess it is.
It's molten though.
Now I have a new fear.
You know, whenever I see one of those.
Okay.
Short range homing.
That is a potential good thing to have.
I think I like it.
I like that.
Let me see if this is going to kill me.
It's just energy orbs.
Yeah, that should be okay.
Right?
We can use that.
Dig a tunnel.
Man, I really want to play worms.
Whenever I dig these tunnels.
That was such a good game.
Hey, yeah, it works.
Decently enough.
Ah, volcanic rock over there?
I just want to go for it a little longer.
Would love to find just a couple more hearts.
I know I'm being a little greedy here.
Think about it like this.
If only I had 100 HP.
Oh, I mean, if I only had 100 HP.
I would still have over half left, you know?
So, in that case, I actually have over half HP left.
Right now.
Think about it like that, okay?
This is another portal.
Do we have a guy?
No.
What's hiding here?
I've been here.
Wait, have I actually explored everything?
That's almost unbelievable.
Is that also molten?
It, man.
So much molten.
Gold.
Ah, here we go.
Maybe something...
No, never mind.
I'm not done playing.
I want to keep going.
I don't want to move on yet.
I accidentally clicked my mouse.
I shit you not.
I have no idea.
Muscle spasm?
I can't explain it, but that was the prompt.
We're getting out of here.
That's it.
I can't be trusted with any of these tools.
We need to leave immediately.
Yep.
That's it.
Let's go.
In the portal.
I'm immediately going to heal.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Okay.
All right.
Hmm.
Fuck, I forgot to go back and re-roll the perks.
I'm an idiot.
Ah!
I guess that's for later, then.
Repelling cape.
Stains drop at a fast rate when moving.
Always cast at random...
No.
Hey!
I think I like that!
Thank you!
Now I just need explosion immunity and damage immunity, just in general.
Also, I also need enemy immunity.
If I can get that, that would be...
Mwah!
You know?
Okay, all of these bubble sparks with triggers, they can go somewhere in this water pool.
I don't enjoy them that much.
Energy orbs, though.
I kind of enjoy it, but they do bounce around, which is scary.
Now, lightning bolt.
That's my jam.
The lightning bolts is what I really crave.
Lightning bolts.
It's what Oliver's crave.
Now it costs 70 mana.
Wait a minute!
This already hurts me!
So putting bloodlust on it is actually just going to boost the damage.
It's not really going to be a negative for me.
If I use lightning bolt, I'm already putting myself in harm's way.
Right?
So...
Hey!
Awesome!
Something like that.
But don't put it on shuffle, of course.
Oh, man.
We only have shuffle ones!
No, we don't.
Never mind.
We have ones over here.
I mean, that would be enough for the one I'm looking to make right now.
Ah, spells per cast, too?
Actually, not...
It's actually okay.
Now that one...
That's a decent one.
I'll take it.
It's half off as well.
Don't want that one.
Let's see.
Double is nice.
Oh, dude!
Double.
Yo!
Hold on.
Oh, dude.
We can make some stuff happen here.
I just got ideas.
In fact...
In fact, hold on.
Hold on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, ideas are forming.
Put this here.
Put these down here.
I have ideas.
We go that.
We go double.
But we also do this.
Double, double.
So this one, two, two.
And the other one is an extra.
Hey!
That's...
Ooh, that's a lot.
Let's see it in action.
Oh!
I see the damage.
366.
Let me move this.
Yeah, as expected.
It only adds like...
It adds...
33 to each.
But shouldn't that be...
399 then?
Wait a minute.
Huh.
So I guess it doesn't apply to the last one.
Or maybe it simply means...
So this is a double.
Which casts this one, which is a double.
And then this double also casts this one after.
So...
The bloodlust here only applies to, I think, these two.
Because it wouldn't make sense for it to apply to only one of these and that one.
Right?
So...
For some reason, this one is being omitted.
From that buff.
But maybe that's just the nature of this.
If I had a triple spell here instead of a double spell, maybe that would have worked in that case.
Maybe the bloodlust here...
Yeah, I'm not quite sure.
Actually.
That confuses me a little bit.
So maybe bloodlust is not needed here at all.
It's not really that much of a damage boost and, you know...
But here's the thing.
Watch this.
We also have a spark bolt with trigger somewhere.
Here.
So if I take that...
And...
Let me put these here.
If I now do this instead...
Is that a bad idea?
Let's see it.
I kind of want to test this.
Hey, it's a...
Oh, it bounces off.
That's...
It is a bit scary.
It's not as reliable as this.
That is reliability right there.
And I do like that when you're handling dangerous stuff such as lightning bolts.
You kind of want to be reliable with it.
Now the question is...
Is that the best one to put it on?
Oh wait, we have a spells per cast too here.
240...
This could be better.
So it's going to cast these two and that one now.
We don't need this.
Hold on.
Right?
That shoots... Hold on.
Is that...
Yeah, it's shooting all three.
So now, quick test, if I now do this...
Is that now going to do 399?
Oh!
That's way more!
Oh, never mind.
Wait, what?
Huh?
Wait.
Oh, wait a minute.
So I... Okay, I'm not quite sure I understand.
Why am I doing more damage randomly?
But this is definitely better.
Right?
450.
Yeah, it's doing more damage.
I mean, obviously.
I'm putting that on here.
That seems like a good use of that.
Or...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Actually, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nope.
Look at this cast a lay on this one.
0.07.
We can do something like this.
Like, this is a decent one already, just with that.
Right?
But, can we make it faster now?
So, the recharge time is the problem, so if we just add a bunch of these...
There's gonna be, like, a little...
Shotgun thingy.
Actually, hold on, we can put it...
Ooh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Quick test here.
If I do that, it's gonna shoot...
Wait.
It's gonna shoot double this one and the next one, but the next one is itself.
Right?
Let me see what it does.
Let me look at the board.
Oh, okay.
No, okay, it's not doing exactly what I thought.
Wait a minute.
Sometimes it shoots...
It shoots two of them.
What if I now...
Hmm.
What if I put two of these?
Oh, no, no, no, that's scary.
Don't do that.
Holy shit.
That could blast off on me.
We don't want that shit.
Bubble spark?
That cost 16 mana.
It costs 10 mana.
I'm feeling like there's something going on here we can...
Oh, wait a minute.
This reduces cast delay, but I need to reduce recharge time on this, basically.
That would be the dream here.
If I do this...
Let's say I shoot...
So, spark bolt is getting shot and when this collides, it shoots a double.
And if one of those doubles is a spark bolt, what is the other one?
The trigger, which then...
Not quite what I expected.
What if we place this?
Sometimes you can find a critical combination that suddenly just changes everything.
I mean, it's the recharge time right now that is messing with us.
Okay, basically, remember in one of the very first runs I ever did, I somehow managed, I think, to circumvent the recharge time completely.
But I don't...
Maybe I'm remembering wrong, actually, but I'm pretty sure I did it somehow.
Let me try a double here.
Do not remember exactly what I did.
I did something for sure.
In fact, we may not need that right now because it's only here to be scary for ourselves, you know?
This one does reduce recharge time, actually.
Maybe I do want to try this in between here.
So let's take that away.
So we have the damage in front.
It shoots that one...
What does this look like?
Yeah, it's actually faster.
It's faster, it's a little bit faster.
It's not bad.
Delayed spell cast, what does this do?
It increases...
No, it doesn't increase speed, it just has a speed.
I'm not so sure.
I'm not seeing anything right here.
You know, the recharge time is the bastard at the moment.
Wait a minute.
Yeah.
Maybe energy orb is even better.
I'm trying to think what would be good here.
That one definitely not in there.
So this one right here, definitely need a double there.
Let me use the one I have here.
That's my, that's my wand.
That's my primary damage wand now.
It's the lightning.
We're going lightning, baby.
And in fact, maybe I will not do this right now and I'll just put the damage here anyway.
Full damage.
Full damage on that.
Yeah, we don't need more than that anyway right now.
Let's calm down.
And let's do...
Put this here.
I do want to keep the homing.
Quadruple scatter I kind of want to keep.
Could be nice.
Now, what do I put on these wands is the question.
I could add a homing to a...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I got idea.
We could actually, we could make a killer wand here with a...
Not spirit bolt, what was the other one called?
Ah, these ones, I threw them in the water.
These guys.
Homing on...
What does this look like again?
Oh, no, no, no, those are the wrong ones.
I want these over here.
Energy orb.
Like, that's cool, right?
I like the energy orb.
Throw that away.
So the issue here, because we have so many of these.
The recharge time is not going to be a factor here because this is just going to be a one big burst.
Also, this short range homing is only going to work on the first, so let's drop that actually.
And we can add a double here just to shoot a couple more.
That's not bad.
And then we do this, remove that, and then use this here instead.
Although that is kind of scary because...
No, is it scary?
I'm so scared of bloodlust after what happened last.
Yeah.
Do we have a digging?
We do, we have that one.
I mean, fuck.
This is fine.
I'm going to go.
We're leaving.
We are leaving.
In fact, I'm going to take some more of these, uh, spark with me.
Get rid of that one.
Get rid of the bomb, actually.
And also get rid of that one.
I just want to have these on me.
All right.
We're good to go, baby.
With electricity immunity as well.
That's going to be a biggie.
Kind of want to try it real quick.
Hey.
This feels great.
So good.
Oh, thank you very much.
Wow.
There's a, uh...
What was the name?
Uku?
Somewhere, I think.
And a sniper.
Let me try this.
Ouch!
You absolute bastard.
How fucking dare you?
Pheromone concentrated mana in Visibleum.
Give me invisibility.
Oh, wait, I'm...
Wait, am I invisible?
No, I need to be not stained.
Come on, get rid of it.
Fuck you.
He likes electricity so much, he'll get some.
God...
Wow!
I'm already getting my ass kicked.
It's actually unreal.
Hey, folks.
Fuck you.
That pissed me off.
Almost lost half HP already because of these snipers.
Ha,
ha, ha.
Man, the power contained in this weapon is unreal.
The problem is it's short range, so maybe it was better to put it on the spark bolt, I'm not sure.
Awesome.
It has a long recharge though.
It's a one shot, one kill type of thing.
Short range sniper.
Also called a shotgun.
Ha, ha.
Rats.
Uh...
How do you not die from that?
Is that a rat frozen?
Look.
What's in here?
Show me.
Ah, no thanks.
I have better digging capabilities.
Freezing vapor, man.
It's the slow killer.
Let's just wait.
Okay.
Any snipers?
Oh, am I already at?
Ah, okay.
I know where I am now.
Kind of want to go back just to get those perks.
And I think we needed 400 gold and we have it.
I think I may do it.
Yeah.
But can we even get up again?
We should be able to.
Maybe not from here, but...
I'm going to get up again and grab the perks.
It's actually very important.
Because if we go through the portal in this level...
We can't really get back up.
This is my one shot at grabbing those perks.
Come on!
Yeah!
Nice.
Oh, and dude, we can even...
We can even get more HP here.
On the way up, that's...
Oh, that's genius.
Oh, we're also going to go on top of the mountain.
And grab that.
You know what feels great in this game?
If you didn't have the knowledge about this...
You wouldn't do it.
Like, it's knowledge that you have, you know?
That is helping you succeed.
So, where is this exactly?
Is it below me or above me?
Below me, I think.
Ah!
Sound is louder up here.
Ah, nice, nice.
Yay!
Fuck yeah.
You're rewarded with additional health.
Up we go.
I do wonder what's making that sound.
Okay.
Nice.
Made it.
Oh, wait.
Um...
Just do this.
Oh, wait, I have an idea.
You can just do this.
Look.
You go like this.
Then you rest here.
And you keep going.
Oh, that's so much better than what I did once before.
I tried to make a path all the way across.
One of the first times.
Yep.
Oh, man, it is kind of scary.
Because I fell through that one somehow.
Like, I made a path and I walked on it and I just...
flipped right... or like, slipped right through.
I have no idea how that actually happened, but it happened.
Now, we could actually go heal.
We know where there's a heal.
Ah, should I though?
The heals are very important.
That heal could come in clutch later on.
But the thing is, I think you have to adopt a mindset of...
Let's just first get to the endgame before we start worrying about...
the endgame, you know what I mean?
So I may actually just go grab it.
You're gonna end up dying too much when you try to play for the endgame.
Because you never get to the endgame.
I'm gonna heal.
But I'm actually gonna go up first and grab the extra health upstairs because...
That makes sense, I think.
Teleportation.
I do wonder what is the difference between unstable teleportation and teleportation.
I don't think I've actually thought about that...
ever.
What is the difference?
Yeah, what the hell is the difference?
Because when I get hit with teleportation, I teleport randomly also.
Somewhere.
What the hell?
I never thought about that.
Maybe it lasts longer or something.
Or maybe it's faster, you know, you teleport to places faster per second.
We can dig with this, I think.
Oh yeah, definitely.
Go up here.
Very nice.
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait.
Did I just pick that up twice?
What just happened?
I got a text saying... orb acquired and then it... and then I picked it up after.
I have no idea what just happened there.
That's odd.
I kind of... F11.
Shit.
Okay, whatever.
Maybe it's just when you release the... the health, you know?
That's when you get that message.
And then when you pick it up, you actually get the, oh, your health was increased to X amount.
I feel so free not having to worry about where my wand is in relation to liquids right now.
Especially water.
Or metal.
Now we're gonna go...
Oh, and we can dig everywhere now.
Maybe... This is an opportunity to explore all these levels again, actually.
This is not bad.
I like this.
In fact, we may even be strong enough to, like, just a little bit maybe explore the ancient laboratory.
I heard that noise again now.
Who is it?
There's someone hidden here making noises.
Like a throwing noise.
Who is it?
Oh.
Oh, but wait, we can't see shit.
I didn't think about that.
Why am I such an idiot?
Oh, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We can dig.
We can drain the shit out of this place.
We don't care.
We don't care at all.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Let me drain over here.
It's drain time.
I
knew that was going to happen, but I figured, okay, I'm swimming in water.
I'm not going to fall down into the beam.
Oh, it's so scary.
Also, I'm slippery right now, so that doesn't help.
Somehow I had oil on me.
But it's fine.
We're going to heal anyway.
Drain it.
Yes.
Oh, I'm dying.
I couldn't breathe in the steam.
Let's be careful with that.
Okay.
Can I get rid of the steam like this?
No, not really.
The steam is just there.
Oh.
Didn't mean to shoot that.
Now we dig here.
Wait, why can't I see here suddenly?
I can... You see that?
I can slightly see.
Wait, did I just... Wait a minute.
Am I revealing?
Ah, the water look is draining completely.
This is nice.
This is real good.
In fact, let me make a channel.
Okay, it's not going as fast as I would like.
This may be okay.
So it was like somewhere here, no?
Oh no, that's too scary.
I need to drain.
We gotta drain it all.
It's simply... Imagine if I died in there now, that would be an absolute fucking disaster.
Of epic proportions though.
You know?
How am I gonna do this?
Maybe here.
I don't know where to drain it?
I guess I could just evaporate it slowly but surely?
The things you do to get some health in this game, huh?
I mean, it's working.
It's definitely working.
This is kind of effective.
And it makes the water drain down here because I lower the level.
This is a win-win.
The problem is the steam, but that will dissipate.
Hopefully, the steam does disappear, right?
Let me see over here.
Yeah, it definitely does.
This
may not be the best way to do it, I realize.
I could just... Also, I'm scared of digging through this in case I somehow anger the gods.
That's another thing.
Are we at the point?
Did we actually do it?
Oh, where is the steam?
Steam.
Right.
Steam, you can't breathe.
Actually, collect the water.
Let's just wait for this to...
Can I get rid of the steam with...
Yo, is that lighting up the area?
Oh!
Did you see that?
It's lighting it!
Oh, we're saved!
I can see!
Yes!
Oh, that's glorious!
Fuck yeah!
Very nice!
Okay, man, there it is!
That's actually good to know.
Produces a bit of light.
What was this one?
The chili egg.
No, wait, that just contains...
like, a pheromoned enemy, no?
Okay, so, I think...
Hemisphere has been explored.
It's time to explore the rest of...
this place.
And that is also where we have the perks!
In fact, can I not just...
Nah, that's gonna take too long.
Are these things gonna fall on me?
I'm so scared.
Yeah, let's not take any chances there.
Can I blow up with any...
Oh, that's much better!
Lovely.
Lovely stuff.
This wand kinda sucks, honestly.
I made a shitty wand here.
This is a bad wand.
There we go!
Unlimited spells!
We are one step closer...
with the homing...
to the rock dream.
Yes!
The rock dream is real.
Hold on, do I wanna buy anything while I'm here?
No, I have 60 gold.
Nah, I don't think I...
Oh, refresher maybe.
No, no, no, no, we're gonna save that in case we find healing spell.
Imagine that, we find healing spell, that refresher is gonna be insane later on.
Hell yeah.
Okay, so to the west of here, there is the...
fungal caverns.
I wanna get there now.
I think we have quite a lot of power...
to explore that place.
And also map it out properly.
Okay, that's an... empty area.
I just realized, maybe I should have put in firebolt somewhere...
with a homing, that would have been cool.
Because we have unlimited spells now.
But... it's fine.
Hello!
Oh!
That indicator right there is...
making me think that is not good.
Aha!
I kinda wanna see this.
Hold on.
What is this?
What is that thing?
Oh, it's a piece of the chest.
Okay, nevermind.
Yep!
That was a mimic!
Funny thing is, I just haven't seen them really.
I just know they exist.
You know, like, what do they even look like?
Maybe just a chest.
Okay, I'm not afraid of anyone now, because I have this.
Fuck you!
This is the guy that really messed with me last time.
It feels so good to teach him a lesson.
Like, I'm back, baby.
Don't you even think about it?
Oh, I hate those.
That's gonna... fill me with teleportation.
transportation.
Like, make me randomly teleport.
Oh my god.
It flew closer to me, and then exploded right next to me.
Goddammit.
What's that?
Toxic sludge?
I don't want that here!
This is a bad spot for this spell.
Why is this place so difficult, man?
Aluminum.
See ya.
The guy above me?
Am I brave enough?
Dude, we could go tripping.
If we wanted to.
It could happen.
Uh...
There's a bunch of hammerses.
Wait, why is that slowing down so much?
Look at the projectiles.
Uh-oh, there's a thingy.
What the hell is happening here?
Oh, oh!
What
is it about this place?
Yeah, kill me!
Fucking kill me, I hate this place.
I'm never coming to this place again.
I'm done.
Fungal caverns?
Never.
Again.
It's always like this, dude.
I swear, it's every time.
That is the hardest area in the game.
Change my mind.
Holy shit.
I'm tilted right now.
I came in there with like a 300 HP, a fucking electrical explosion and shit.
I had all the perks, you know, I was set.
And the game's like, fuck you.
And I'm dead, you know?
Wow!
Okay, next time I'm coming back there, I have 2,000 HP.
And a wand.
And basically damage immunity.
I don't know if that's even a thing, you know, but...
I guess if I get melee immunity, electricity immunity, fire immunity, toxic immunity, all the immunities, I guess I'm damage immune?
Is it even possible to get that?
Imagine getting all of those.
But at that point, then I'm coming back.
Fuck that place so much.
The hardest place in the game.
For me.
There.
Slash rant, I'm done.
That was annoying.
But that's fine.
What is happening here?
Look at this.
This is weird looking, isn't it?
I don't think I've seen this before.
What the... almost looked like...
temple.
Wait a minute, something's glowing in there.
Oh, you know what?
I thought, I think that was just the gold from the guy I just killed.
I thought something was hiding in there.
That place looked special to me, you know?
Oh, look at them avoiding it.
What does?
I shall not become impatient.
No, sir.
We have water.
That's good.
It's a good start.
Also, I need to update my death counter.
So I guess that is now 66.
Nice.
Ah, there's... Oh wait, but I can't get through holes right now.
Okay, wait, wait, this looks suspicious.
Look at this.
Why is there a little hole there?
Isn't that weird?
Do we need to do something here?
What is happening?
Oh, come on!
Fuck you!
I should have dodged upwards there.
I thought I could make it to the water in time.
Boy, was I wrong.
I'm slippery like an eel.
Oh,
so there's someone down here who emits that aura.
To this day, I still don't understand this aura of what it does.
It's a big aura as well.
How do I get down there?
Maybe I bombed this place.
That way I also destroy the coal.
Whoa, that was close.
I stood a little too close there.
Wait, I've seen one of these.
Wait, Runestone of Emptiness?
What the shit is that?
Oh, do I feel like kicking it?
I don't remember what happened.
I remember this though.
Now it stops.
Now it begins.
Huh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, it's a shield.
Is it not?
Look at my projectiles here.
They get interrupted.
Huh.
But, okay, so it doesn't quite help me that my projectiles get interrupted.
I want my enemy's projectiles to get interrupted.
Yo, teleport!
And, dude, this... what a trick that wand is, huh?
That's nice.
I feel much better already.
That's great.
I'm not going to use it though.
I'm just going to throw a dynamite in the direction I'm teleporting.
I mean, I guess it could be useful.
Wait, why did that... it shoots that one?
Why did that not shoot a dynamite just now?
Am I tripping?
Shouldn't that have shot a dynamite?
It shot a triplicate.
But I haven't used this one before.
Huh.
Maybe someone else used it in the game.
I wonder if that counts.
If someone else uses it first and I pick it up and I use it.
Is the next spell going to cast in that case?
Nice.
Oh!
That guy came jumping.
He's going to kill him.
Get him!
Oh, that works.
That's beautiful.
Thank you for that.
Thank you very much.
What's up, Barney?
Another wand?
I can get in there.
Because look at this.
That may be a good location already for it.
Let's get it a little closer.
So if I aim up like this... Oh, that's so much more reliable now.
Okay, not quite.
I guess we have to bomb the rest.
Just
do it.
Energy spheres.
Terrible mana charge speed, but that's fine.
Mana max is quite high.
And this is the superior spell, in my opinion.
Oh, that's going to take a while.
Fuck it.
He's now right here.
Oh, a heart!
Very nice.
Do I have a nice way of... Wait, doesn't this?
No, it doesn't.
I really want to... I want to use this, but I'm scared.
If I'm fast enough, I can teleport out of here.
Watch this.
Wait.
Oh,
it's never going to shoot this!
And you know why?
Because of mana.
Yes!
I was so lucky there.
Wow.
Incredible.
So basically what happens is, it's going to shoot the triple kit first.
You know?
With the tele... Yeah, it's going to shoot a triple kit, but I don't have enough for that.
Okay,
yeah, it's going to shoot both.
And if I don't have enough mana, then max is only going to shoot the teleport.
That's what happened there.
That was a bit risky on my part.
In other words, it's safe to use.
Okay, maybe not there.
Let's use it here.
Ho!
It's actually kind of cool the way the... it digs and teleports at the same time.
That's kind of a unique dynamic there.
You know, it allows you to quickly get through small crevices that you make with the same wand.
This guy has a wand.
Ah!
Dumbass!
I guess that revealed what's on this wand.
A bit of burst of air.
Yo, the wand slaps.
Ah!
I think I may just take it.
Thanks!
That's a great wand.
These guys can fight.
I don't care.
Oh, look at the Hamish congregation.
That was brutal.
Ooh!
Wow!
What a shot!
That guy has the aim of a god.
I died, though.
What is that?
Acceleration.
Very cool.
I kind of wanted to try something against the fire dude, but if I see another one, I'm going to try it next time.
What if I do this?
Here, throw at me.
Did that just...
Okay, so... I'm not quite sure.
Throw.
Yeah, look.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, it doesn't deflect them.
It completely removes them.
The projectiles get completely... they just disappear.
Isn't that interesting?
Dude, I have ideas with this now.
If I bring this to a boss, and I use a spell that... like a melee spell.
Melee spell.
Something very close by, you know?
That will eliminate all of his projectiles, basically.
When I stand in it.
Oh, look at this fucker.
Yeah, throw.
Look, he can't!
He can't!
You mad, bro?
You're so mad!
Hold on, uh...
Let's not move out of it.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Yeah, come up here.
Come up here.
I dare you.
I double dare you, motherfucker.
Oh, God!
This is kind of a disaster right now.
Oh, wait, I have this.
Oh!
Oh, wait, that... that... I'm almost dead.
That was a terrible duel.
Absolutely terrible.
It's not going well.
Okay.
Amos.
It is a bit scary, though, because I teleport straight in.
Uh, hello, Barney?
Here we go.
Collapsed mines.
So it's not always that it's here, but it's sometimes here.
Percircium.
I like that.
Drink it.
Drink a bunch of it.
Oh!
Jesus Christ, that did a lot of damage!
Wow!
I feel like I'm already dead.
This is going terrible.
Oh, no, these guys have a lot of HP.
In fact, that is for you.
Follow them!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
No!
Oh, wait, he's my friend now.
Hey, what's up, friends?
Never mind, he's not my friend.
He is not my friend.
Oh, I can't get that gold.
I wonder why it's called a berserk curse.
Makes me feel like it's not only positives you get with that.
And there's some hidden debuff that I'm not aware of.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
That is so annoying.
He's spraying on me, even in death.
Getting a last laugh here, huh?
Give me water.
Oh, man, this is bad.
I think it's time to just move on.
It pains me to say it, but...
Yeah, look at all this.
This is for you.
Get him.
Ah, close.
Yeah, let's make our way out.
We have a lot of gold.
It's actually not that bad.
The gold situation is completely fine.
I don't think we found any... We did find some nice ones, I guess.
But no HP yet.
Wait a minute.
Is there HP in there?
No.
Just wanted a little bit of HP.
Just a taste, you know?
The first portal I see I go through.
Right here.
I can dig.
But I'm not gonna... Oh, is that molten metal?
Yikes.
Let's stay hydrated here and then go through.
How do I get down there?
Oh, hold on, there's a wand.
I'm gonna grab that.
Circle of stillness.
No, thanks.
I'm good.
Uh-oh.
Wait, did the other guy die?
Fuck him.
This is not bad.
Okay, let's see what we got here.
Dropper bolt.
Scatters.
Ah, none of these entice me.
Ah, bot.
What was this?
Wand experimenter.
Firing newly found and unmodified wands yields you.
Now that is quite something.
Thanks.
It's been a while since we had that one.
That is some good shit right there.
Spark bolt, fireball.
Honestly, I'm not a big fan of any of this.
This wand is sick.
Let's put these in here.
And we have a teleport wand now.
Oh, this is fantastic.
Let me see.
That's solid.
Not bad at all.
Bot.
Firebolt.
Oh wait, that's only 25 of them, of course.
I could triplicate bolt on this.
That's not bad either.
Except the spread is a little too intense there.
So it's like a close quarter thing.
0.08.
Ooh, wait, wait, wait.
Ah, no, no, the mana there is bad.
What about this one?
0.18, 0.58 mana charge speed is nice.
I think I like this.
It's a solid wand.
It does the job.
Yeah.
And maybe I can also grab...
Electric torch.
Dropper bolt.
I don't know if I want any of this, man.
Now, this one was a little interesting.
Small explosions appear randomly over a large area.
And they can't damage me.
I tested this.
So we have teleport, we have damage.
We could put this in here for a bit of digging.
And then some more digging.
Yeah, let's just do that.
Yeah.
It's not the best, but you know, it'll do.
Unless...
If we want to dig, why don't we have a drill?
Hey!
Wait, why is that different?
Castelay minus 0.58.
Oh, it also reduces recharge, but why...
Ha!
The order matters on this one!
Almost as if this is some kind of modifier.
Why does the order matter?
That's interesting.
Hold on.
Okay, it's almost the same, that's... wow.
Okay, well, cool, I guess.
And then we have dynamite, not bad.
I think we're gonna roll with this.
This is a great starter.
Get up.
I can dig it.
And we get to heal whatever we want now, pretty much.
So, that's a crazy perk.
Probably one of the best that I've found so far.
Let me test this now.
Decent digging.
Hell yeah, that is definitely good enough in a pinch.
Concentrated mana.
Return.
Now we have this, that's also good to know.
Hey!
Whoa!
Wow, look at that beam.
Yeah,
the energy sphere is great.
Hell yeah.
Just a solid spell, you know?
Excuse me, what do we have there?
Let me get in there.
A bit of a shop.
Black hole.
Another electric torch.
Sparkbolt with trigger.
Ooh, explosive projectile.
That's a good one.
I'm taking that.
And I think I'm coming back and save for this.
That could be nice.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, they're killing themselves.
I like how I laugh about that as if I don't do the same thing.
Like, on a regular basis too.
I totally kill myself all the time.
You know, I'm not laughing at them, I'm laughing with them.
At the whole idea of killing yourself.
That was a bit too close.
Sweet.
I have enough gold now.
Going back to buy that immediately.
Thanks.
I think I may even buy the black hole.
It's just, I feel like it's not...
Okay, the black hole is cool.
But I feel like it's not that useful when you only have one of them.
Because even unlimited spells is not actually going to fix that problem.
But the only way around it is to have like a shit ton of them.
So let's say you find a wand that already has like ten.
That's when you consider, okay.
Maybe I want to take this with me.
But a single spell of black hole is just not good, in my opinion.
Okay.
Nothing there.
This way.
Oh, watch this.
Yeah!
That's exactly what I imagine would happen in my mind.
Rarely things align like that.
How am I...
Poisoned, huh?
I went in water.
Heh.
Yeah!
Fantastic!
That was fun.
I want to do more kills like that.
That's just too funny.
In fact, I wonder.
Hold on.
Let me try something.
Can I actually?
Hold on.
Oh wait, I can't...
Damn it!
Okay, I'm going to test on the next one.
Oh yeah, it fucks with my projectiles now.
Hold on.
I'm going to try and throw this in the face of someone.
Because that would be a great use of this if that actually works.
Oh, wait a minute.
Have I been here?
Does that mind?
Oh!
Now that's a digging wand.
In fact, it's just straight up better than that.
Instead of one dynamite, give me a million.
Thanks.
Thank you very much.
Hey, you like that?
It fucking worked!
And not only that, that did a lot of damage.
Are you kidding me?
I love this game, man.
Holy shit.
You know, you think of something, you try it and it just works.
Oh god, I can't shoot him now.
Okay, oh wait, I can turn it off though!
Yeah, this guy has the same problem.
We can't really hit each other.
So watch this.
Now it's off.
So every time I throw it now...
No, no, no, it's gonna activate when you throw it.
Okay.
Oh man, that sucks.
I could otherwise just run around with this and fucking throw it on people.
I mean, I still can, but you know.
Okay, watch this.
How did you see me?
Shit!
Don't
even...
Fuck you, man!
I tried kicking him and I missed and he was meleeing me.
That was a real duel just now.
How did I not kick him once?
That's unbelievable.
I really wanted to teach him a lesson, you know?
I guess I was the one who was taught a lesson there.
Shaking intensifies.
No idea what's happening.
Something violent is going on somewhere.
Man, this would be the perfect weapon if it wasn't for the projectile field that it has.
What was it called again?
Runestone of Emptiness.
Weirdly, one of the few items you find that isn't in Finnish.
Right?
Like, what the hell?
That's so rare.
Usually they have these weird names.
Whoops.
Dude, I just had an idea.
What if you just used a tablet?
I'm gonna try that.
If I pick up a tablet... I mean, you could, you can throw that shit.
That's one of the few things you can pick up and take with you, right?
Mix it.
Horizontal path.
Yo!
Aww, it's shuffle.
No.
But?
Nope.
I don't want it.
God damn, that guy almost hit me.
And he would, yeah, he's gonna hit that fireworks.
Aww.
Yeah, you mad now?
You can't hit me down there.
Phew!
What should I use?
Hey, that works.
Oh wait, I'm healing as well!
I forgot about this!
I forgot I had this perk!
That's lovely.
I completely forgot I had that.
I feel great now being reminded that I have that.
I was so occupied with the whole throwing this thing.
Mmm, okay.
Go this way around.
Aww, yeah.
Nope.
Go here.
Can I...?
Yes, I can.
That's actually a solid way to...
Um...
I know I said I wouldn't go in here.
And I'm not gonna go in there.
Holy shit!
That bomb came from heaven!
Are you actually kidding me?
What the hell was that?
I can heal.
I cannot heal.
No, I can't heal.
Also, I forgot I still have... I have teleport.
I have to remember.
What is there?
What is that thing down there?
Is that a want?
Look at it!
I'm so confused.
How is that not a want?
Okay, we found the portal area.
Mmm... Oh, here we go, here we go.
So that's the one I had before.
Will that count for healing now?
No, it won't.
I had to test, though.
I should be digging more.
I have lots of these.
Maybe aim a bit more carefully here.
Come on, man.
Argh!
That's what happens when you have so much of things, you start to not be careful with it.
That was not worth it.
Especially because I've already been here anyway.
But there is someone below me.
That lava almost hit me in the eye.
Let's take out this fire.
Yeah!
A want!
That means healing!
Mana...
Hey!
Nice!
Sweet.
What just happened there?
I swear, this perk right here, the healing with the wands, is something else.
It is so damn good.
Because there's literally wands everywhere, right?
Wow, you can shoot this fast as well.
I guess I have a very short cast delay on it.
And recharge time.
I could go through here, no?
Oh, yeah.
Do I want to go in there?
I don't, right?
No, no, no.
I come back with 2K HP and complete damage immunity.
That was my promise to myself.
Although...
Hmm...
No.
Nope!
I'm not doing it.
But we only have 300 gold.
I'm so torn.
Actually doesn't want there.
Ah, dig inside.
Why is that so hard to destroy?
What is this?
I'm kind of raw.
Oh!
A triple!
That's not bad!
Linear arc makes a projectile fly only in cardinal or diagonal lines.
Interesting.
It also removes cast delay or like a little bit of it.
And adds damage.
Huh!
That is actually interesting.
I will take it.
Maybe I can just stick my head in here and just take a peek.
No, no, no, no.
No, we're leaving.
What is happening here?
Why are projectiles being like that?
There's clearly something I'm not getting here.
Why are they...
Look at this!
What is that?
Ambrosia?
Rip?
I kind of wanted that.
What?
Oh, I'm standing in this.
I'm fine.
Haha!
Look at this house!
Is that broken as fuck?
Come here!
Oh, but he also has it.
Look.
Don't you hit me with that.
Oh, what's up, man?
I see you also have it, huh?
Oh, never mind.
Look at all these buddies.
Okay, let's not...
No, I'm leaving.
Nope, I'm not going in there.
Am I?
No, I'm not going.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh!
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, will you please...
Please!
Leave me alone!
For God's sakes!
While I fix my inventory.
Oh, you know what?
Oh, you like that?
How about that?
Huh?
God, I felt good!
Oh, God.
This is actually not working to my advantage, having that stone right there.
It's working against me.
That was solid, though.
That one shot at him, that was insane.
Throw that shit away.
Grab that instead.
And then here...
Someone wants to tangle.
Oh, wait, I haven't shot this yet.
Heal me up.
Oh, God.
Oh, but this only goes in diagonal shit.
Where'd you go?
Where have you gone?
Where did the wand go?
Oh, you fucked...
Motherfucker!
He took the wand!
Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me?
I gotta say, though, he kicked my ass.
This guy...
This guy fucked me.
He took me to the shit.
Wow!
I got outplayed there.
Holy shit.
I came back for the plasma wand.
I was like, what the hell is my wand?
Two seconds later, I die to that wand.
Oh!
Hold on, I need to update the death counter.
This thing is just going up and up and up today.
In fact, I may actually be one higher than I have it written right now.
I forget if I updated all of them, but...
Also, for some reason, I am leaking today.
I gotta take a piss again.
All
right, let's go.
Let's mess up some people.
Honestly, I'm not mad about that death at all, because it was so funny.
That's one of the... that was actually hilarious.
Oh, would you look at this now?
I have a little wand there.
I can use it later.
You know the...
Okay, so right now, whenever I see a broken wand, inside of me, I feel, oh, that's great for later.
You know?
It's like this feeling of hope that I get when I find it.
And I hope to get that same feeling from some of the other items in the game that I still don't know what to do, you know?
Like, up until that point, I looked at those things as useless.
But when I found out their true purpose, everything changed, right?
Obviously.
So, I'm just looking forward to that.
Finding more of those uses for other items.
Bouncing burst, I think that's the worst starting spell.
But maybe I'm just not good at using it.
What is that?
I think that is...
Oh, never mind, I was going to guess wrong.
Levitation.
Not bad.
That means things can happen.
Also, I am currently in possession of mud.
I thought it was swamp water.
Um, that's not good.
We need to get that fixed ASAP.
In fact, that is actually...
If I catch fire right now, I do not have a good time.
So, how about we sort of get rid of it and get some water?
What's that?
Concentrated mana?
I will take it just because it's not a bottle.
Where do we have water?
I know where
there's lava.
That doesn't help me.
Okay, you know what?
The bouncing burst when you have a low castile is not too terrible.
You know, it'll do.
Here's some water.
Let's get rid of the mud.
And it really just is mud.
It's the mountain of mud.
Get rid of it.
There we go.
Nice.
Now we're set.
Sweet.
I saw another one.
There you are.
That's scary.
Come here, you.
Burn.
Or not.
Man.
Where are the wands?
But I'm not complaining because I just found this.
I guess I was complaining, but then the game was immediately...
Okay, fine, here.
Take it.
Another potion up there.
Something to dig with.
Something that is not the bomb.
Give me more water.
Nice.
We have full water bottle now.
That's a good start.
Makes me feel way safer against fire.
Also, I don't know if I should be dousing myself in water whenever I could potentially encounter fire.
Is that just something I should be doing?
What I'm wondering.
Because it does reduce the chance of catching fire, I think.
Which isn't bad at all.
You know, it's better to prevent things from happening instead of dealing with things when they have happened.
Oh, look at that.
A treasure chest.
I can get in there.
Oh, what a...
It's raining mud, fire and toxic sludge.
Jesus.
Oh my god.
Can you...
I hate this.
These are such annoying enemies, it's unreal.
Just the fact that they bleed this crap.
So annoying.
And a big guy too.
Oh no.
It's the end of me.
I'm gonna die down here.
Come on.
Okay, that's good.
That's okay.
Now the big guy.
How many are there?
What the hell is happening?
Fucking cleaning up everywhere here after these guys.
What?
How did he just die?
He exploded somehow.
That was weird.
I got him.
Now the big guy.
Huh?
How the hell are these guys exploding?
Is this doing something?
Damage, spread, speed.
That's weird.
Man, the things I do for getting chests here.
Hold on, let me turn this into water.
Water, water, water, water, water.
Wait, why is that not destroying the...
What is that?
Purifying powder.
That's actually really rare.
I see that very rarely.
Let me throw this away.
I'm gonna try this purifying powder on a couple things.
Such as this.
Let's see what this does.
Oh, it's actually a powder.
It collects like that.
Okay.
What if I put it in oil?
Huh?
Makes water.
No fucking shit.
What about blood?
Hold on.
No, I keep equipping that.
Also makes water.
Wait, does this just turn everything into water?
There's no way.
That's pretty cool.
By the way, speaking of liquids and powders.
Maybe what I should be doing is trying to mix more powders with different liquids.
I haven't found a powder pouch in a while.
But when I do, I will try it.
I think I tried some in the past, but nothing really happened.
Also, how do I always end up at 69 HP?
I feel like that happens so often in this game.
Or maybe it's just a...
bias, because you always remember it, you know, and you don't remember the time it doesn't happen.
Now, what's this now?
Berserkium.
There's always an extra max HP underneath.
Something I've noticed.
Like one of these big vats.
What if I put... Oh, wait.
Makes oil?
What?
Oh no, I have oil in there.
Okay.
So it's sitting at the...
So that does nothing to Berserkium.
How am I gonna get in there the best way here?
Probably just destroying, right?
Yeah.
Bomb it!
Paint me a little bit, because Berserkium is nice to have.
And now I do a lot of damage.
No, I don't, because I've already been stained with blood instead.
Shit!
Ha!
Brutal!
Ooh!
I have an idea.
Get him!
Almost worked.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Come here!
They really are bouncing a lot, huh?
My God, man.
This is just a pure mess.
Nice.
Whoa!
Can I do it?
Yeah!
Very cool.
Whoa!
I should have seen that coming.
I mean, I did.
Just a little bit too late.
I saw it coming after the fact.
Oh, wait a minute!
I need to pick up my wand.
I threw it away.
I was like, why do I have a missing slot?
Was it down here?
Hopefully it's not gone.
Oh, no, wait.
Oh, no, it's here, okay.
I thought maybe the lava would have somehow destroyed it.
Good.
I still haven't found a wand.
Are you kidding?
That is so unlucky.
What?
No way.
Ah, okay, almost.
Almost a straight path to the surface.
What a mix.
All right!
Those things are gonna blow.
May as well just make it happen.
Can I safely grab some of this gold?
No, don't do it, don't do it.
You greedy fuck.
We're about to do it, weren't you?
Yes.
Yeah, don't do it.
Hey, Amos.
Almost 300.
And we've almost explored everything.
What is...
happening here?
Is that lava I'm hearing?
I need to get in there and see.
Yep, that is indeed lava.
And a lot of it.
What if I put purifying on that?
Hold on, let me wait for the...
Oh, go.
What?
Huh, it blows up like gunpowder.
Weird.
Well, I'm not going through that portal, that's for sure.
And I'm not going up here either.
Look at this stray lava.
That's a death trap.
Wow.
Yeah, just go.
I'm tempted to not heal.
Teleport!
Wait, what?
Ah, yeah, nice.
And over here we have...
We're back!
We're back, baby!
What the fuck?
Very cool.
Home bringer, burning trail...
What is that one?
Vertical?
No, thanks.
That could be neat.
I want this.
Honestly, just that.
It's...
fine.
Maybe with that attached.
Is that a bad idea?
I feel like...
that will hurt me more than it will hurt my enemies.
You know, that's bad.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're not doing that.
I could go for the double and this.
Let's actually just do that.
Pretty cool.
Does use mana quicker though, so maybe it's not that cool.
What about on this one?
Better, but it's going out of mana super quick, so it's actually not better.
And we have teleport there.
Yep, I'm happy.
I'm happy.
That was a quick mountain there.
Feels good, man.
Quick decisions.
Okay,
I need to play extra careful here.
If I get to, let's say...
20 HP, then I go back in here.
Whoa!
Yeah, that path looks bad.
Let's go this way.
Damn it.
Ah, I won't!
And we can get there because we have digging capability.
Oh, that's going to take a while.
I'm not feeling that.
Let's see if we can't find an alternate path.
Oh, shit!
That was lava on the ground!
Small pixels of it.
Something below this?
Jeez!
I'm just getting hit from all sides right now.
I'm playing terribly.
Don't you dare hit me again.
I have to remember I have teleport.
Cool.
Here's my plan.
Okay, not bad.
And then maybe there's some coal here.
Nah, from below maybe.
Any enemies here?
Looks relatively safe.
Okay, nice.
I mean, this is fine.
Especially with teleport bolt.
Oh!
There's a chance of that happening, I knew that.
And it happened.
Now finally a new wand.
I like it.
That's a decent wand.
Very good.
And it's almost time to go heal.
Don't get hit by that.
Okay, he died.
Let's just... let's just chill for a minute here.
Wait for the enemies to come into my range.
Something below me, I think.
It died?
What is going on here?
Hello.
I'm playing so focused right now.
I'm in gaming mode.
I saw that pixel.
The hell?
Aight!
It burned away.
Gunpowder.
Whoa!
Come on.
Next!
The bush was moving.
Scared me a little bit.
Fill up on water.
And I think it's time to head back and heal.
So let's sort of go up and left.
As much as we can.
Here I have to go right, though.
Oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Water!
Watch this!
Yes!
Do I have enough?
I need to find more.
Oh yeah, there's plenty.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Hopefully the blood at the bottom there is not going to cause an issue.
Wait, how much?
It could be another liquid.
I just remembered the triangle there.
Was the same as last time, no?
It was definitely not more than up to my feet, obviously.
Okay, wait, there's not water.
It's something else.
Oh no.
What could it be?
Triangle inside...
a cube.
With dots around it.
And a cloud?
Hmm, I'm not sure.
Levitation?
Fly to the clouds, maybe?
I could try that, but I have to empty this first.
That would be...
Hold on.
Gotta get rid of this.
Where is that?
Molten... Molten gold, nah.
Ah, nice, and now it's just gold.
Actually good to know you can do that.
I was wondering.
Here we go.
Ah, it's going to be a pain to empty this, though.
Honestly, I have no clue what it could mean.
Maybe the blood at the bottom is messing with me.
Can I get rid of that?
I did, uh...
On accident, oops, I'm not...
I did on accident fill it up with a little bit of blood down there, that was not my intention.
And also, it started off with water inside of it.
So I feel like it's gotta be water.
So maybe the blood is fucking it up.
Fuck!
I give up.
I don't wanna try every liquid right now.
I feel, okay, you know what, here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna explore around it and see if there's an indicator liquid.
Like, there's obviously water here and there was water inside of it to begin with.
So I'm leaning towards something water and without the blood, right?
But maybe there's something, some other liquid.
We're gonna try.
Nope.
Could be, no, it's not, it could be lava.
No, how do I even get lava?
It's gotta be in something with this.
Three dots and a diamond.
Inside a wine glass, look at the thing.
I am not sure.
I was hoping that would be some liquid nearby that would, oh, you know, speaking of liquids, we kinda need some water in this.
Yeah, we gotta go grab some water.
Just for safety.
And also, we wanted to go heal, right?
That was my entire plan.
So I'm actually gonna do that first.
We gotta play this safe.
Back to healing.
Up and to the left.
Except not here.
Wait, where?
Scary stuff.
Ah, here we go, here we go.
Now I just gotta get through this.
But that's fine.
Couldn't be too hard.
In fact, I just need to make a small crack.
There we go.
Nice.
Cool.
This is efficiency, people.
And now let's not squander this HP.
This opportunity.
Don't blow it.
I'm gonna go west now.
Except I'm not.
Yes, I am.
Yeah, that's dangerous.
Aw, look at all the lava from that one guy.
Fucking ruined.
There's an entire area to stand on now.
Oh my god, stop!
What do I do?
I squatter the opportunity immediately.
What is wrong?
It's like a mental thing, I swear to god.
It's like as soon as I hit a peak, I immediately throw it all away.
I can't explain what's wrong with me.
Why do I do this?
What's that?
Gunpowder?
Intoxic slug?
Nobody likes that.
But I do like another wand.
Fly downwards.
Reduces castelay and also projectile-speeding increase on that.
Sure, I mean, I don't have any other wand, so why wouldn't I?
I'll take that.
What was that?
Massive explosion hurt.
Ooh.
That guy is stuck in the wall?
What the hell happened here?
Oh my god, from both sides?
They're so smart!
The pincer attack!
I'm showered and poisoned now.
Aw, man.
Duh.
Yeah, this is not the place to be.
It is just not.
These are the guys blowing up.
Guys, come on.
Were they just throwing dynamites at each other?
Aw, not this place.
I feel like, okay, here's the thing.
Here's what I feel like.
First of all, we're gonna heal with this, because I actually almost forgot that we had this.
There we go.
I feel like...
I need to get over my fear of this place.
I can't be scared of it.
I need to get in here.
And do some damage.
And you know what?
Let's get high as fuck.
That's how we're gonna cope with things.
We're gonna get high, okay?
That sounds like fun.
Oh god.
There was so much gold I left on the table there.
Ghostbuster!
It's been a minute.
Chaotic polymorphine?
Yikes.
Maybe I do want that.
There you go, buddy.
Ha ha!
Turn into...
Uh, something bad.
That's not good.
Maybe I fucked up turning him into that.
Huh?
Oh, it's a rat!
Ah, I see.
I see.
This shouldn't hurt me, right?
Oh god, these things explode.
Yep.
Ooh.
Oh!
Oh, here we go!
Holy shit!
Okay, a spell refresh on that.
And the... okay, I'm happy I went in here.
Holy shit.
It's happening.
Oh, can I not dig that?
Aw, come on!
No!
Okay, thank god.
Ah, wait, that's a rat.
Maybe we're okay.
Let's see this.
That looks... dangerous.
But it looks fun.
We can use this to get out of here.
And heal a little bit.
Pour three of them.
Hell yeah!
Uh-oh.
Oh, he is dead!
Ha-ha.
Oh, toxic!
No!
Doesn't purify it.
I thought of all the things, that would be the one.
You know?
But okay.
Guess not.
Oh, wait, don't take that yet.
I kind of want to kill these guys.
Just because.
That does not dig.
No way.
Alright, switch it back.
Okay, I'm liking this place.
What's that?
Kiva Skivi.
You know what?
Throw that away.
Oh no, not this guy.
Okay, he's dead.
Let's go this way.
And let's be super careful.
Uh, there's a frog.
There's actually two of them.
The frogs scare me.
They do so much damage, they have so much range.
Are you kidding?
Oh yeah, that works.
Oh wait, this is healing, I shouldn't use it.
Bro, this guy is not gonna die.
This is so inaccurate.
Nope.
That ain't happening.
The circular, I like it.
Okay, not too bad, not too bad.
Will you stop hitting me with your tongue?
Maybe with this berserkium I can do something.
Yeah, there we go.
Finally I got him.
Are we rewarded for that?
Sort of.
Well, any wand is a reward right now because of our perks.
Oh, okay.
That's scary.
It randomly shoots, yeah, that's the thing.
Oh my god.
So frickin' annoying.
You are in such an annoying spot, you know that, sir?
There we go.
And what's this now?
A little wand.
Okay, nice.
You working on your abs?
He's still not dead.
Bro, it is a good I have the wand healing.
Oh, I'm stuck in here.
Oh, lordy!
Remove the debuff!
That's the sound of my frustration, okay?
Heal me.
Heal me!
What's this?
Oh, not that.
That's fine.
Let's try it.
Yeah!
It heals me, that's fine.
Boink.
Nice.
How much damage does that do again?
75.
Holy shit.
Formation behind your back?
Okay.
That looks scary.
But it's heal.
This is pure chaos.
Is that honey?
Look at that.
What if I eat honey?
Oh.
Uh, sir?
Eat it.
Oh, no, wait, I ate mushroom.
That's fine.
I actually wanted to do that anyway.
Let me just calm down for a second and then we can do it.
Oh my god, I hate these fucking...
You know what?
Toxic immunity would be incredible.
Or some kind of poison immunity or sludge immunity.
Green immunity is what I want.
Can I have that place?
It may even be worse than fire for me.
I swear to god, it's just the worst.
It's like sand, you know?
It's small, crumbly, and it gets everywhere.
The same thing here.
Oh.
Stop it, will you?
That guy's gonna be an issue.
Um, okay, you can't eat the honey.
It's unfortunate.
A shiny orb.
Thanks.
Did I try this?
Sure I did not.
Or did I?
No, I didn't.
But I'm not finished healing with this one yet.
So that, right, that, this here looks like death.
Let's do the logical thing here and play it so slow.
Like...
Ugh!
It almost happened again in here.
It almost happened again.
I'm stuck in the terrain!
Come on!
Oh, I'm in poison now.
This is a disaster.
Come on, next.
You like that?
How about you?
Like that?
How about that?
Yeah?
That good?
As long as you keep funneling in one at a time, I can deal with it.
Can I though?
Maybe I can.
Then we grab this one over here and heal now.
Oh man, this perk has saved my ass.
Time and time again.
Such a good perk.
It's making up for all my dumb decisions, you know?
Wait, did I just?
Ah shit.
Change it back.
Now we heal up.
Did I just destroy a book?
I saw a book!
Oh no!
Oh fuck.
Sparkbowl with timer.
More bombs.
All these bombs.
Holy wand amount!
There's wands everywhere.
Maybe I should just be bombing everybody.
Holy crap, it shoots for a time.
I'm stuck.
You like bombs?
Like this place is just pure chaos.
It's the most chaotic region ever.
Oh, this one always casts speed up.
That's pretty dope.
I actually kind of like that.
Let's heal with that.
Grab that.
I'm experimenting so much with wands.
Will you please die?
What the hell?
They are so annoying.
It's unreal how annoying they are.
Holy shit.
I'm losing my damn mind.
Can't even use the right wand here in frustration.
Okay, you know what?
I feel like a lot of enemies in this game are the worst enemies in the game.
Which is a paradox, because that logically cannot be.
But it somehow is.
You know what I mean?
Every enemy is the worst enemy in the game.
I cannot get through there.
Even though I want to.
Look at all that blood.
What is this one again?
The bomb one.
Will I have superior bombs?
Uh oh.
Are you going to be an issue?
Okay.
Probably shouldn't have done that by the way, because they were still healing on that wand.
But whatever.
We have a new one.
Whoa!
Alright!
Sweet!
I shouldn't have done that.
Fuck.
But never mind, there's two more wands.
So everything's fine.
Oh, chaotic polymorphine?
Hell no.
What a spot I'm trapped in here.
Oh!
Fungal soil pouch!
Hello!
Is that another word for a bag of drugs?
Because I would love that.
Bombs.
Hell yeah.
Ambrosia!
Well played!
Well played Oliver!
Fucking god gamer right here.
Incredible performance.
Lovely stuff there.
You are the best.
God damn.
Nobody can top you.
It's just on another level, completely.
What's happening here?
What's this?
Oh, another wand in there?
I will take that.
Uh, yeah.
Water potion!
That's the boring...
That's a very boring wand.
No thanks.
Now that wand, I guarantee you it's going to be insane.
Watch.
Uh?
What is that?
Makes a projectile cast tentacles in random directions.
So it's like the saw blade thing, but with tentacles.
That could be interesting.
And it's a modifier on the fire bolt here.
Do I want that?
I feel like I kind of want to keep these luminous drills.
Okay, it's time to get high.
Never mind, hold on, we got to deal with this guy first.
Can't get high with ghost busters around.
Was this guy like half invisible?
What happened there?
Look at him, they're all like half gone.
What the fuck is going on there?
Say what?
Yo, look at all the mushrooms.
Just a dynamite.
I'll take it to heal though.
Wait, where's my...
Oh, I can't breathe in the mushroom.
Oh god, I have no more water.
Oh no!
This is a disaster.
Blood, take the blood.
Was that concentrated mana?
No thanks.
Let me also heal once more.
Heal me up.
This perk is insane.
The best perk ever.
It may actually be the best perk in the game.
So far for me, I think this tops everything.
And you know why?
Because it saves my ass again and again and again.
I would have been dead 20 times already.
I mean, if I hadn't had this perk, I would have gone to the next level of course.
It allows me to stay in here and do things.
And that is insane.
Give me that back.
And then, there was another one there.
No wait, what was it?
I'm gonna eat all this weird fungus now.
Watch.
You can try this at home.
You can be just like me.
Oh, I'm...
I'm trippin'.
In fact, I'm taking damage.
Oh, the lava echoing and shifting in colors.
Why am I still... fucking poisoned?
Concentrate on mana.
Okay, so lava, huh?
I wonder what that has become.
Get him.
Imagine if it changed the green stuff into water.
Wouldn't that be the dream?
Holy shit.
Wow.
Yeah, I already used this entire wand.
Dang it.
Gotta find a new one.
I'm like a drug addict, you know, just looking for my next high in here.
Meaning the wands.
And also, I guess, the fungi, but...
BAM!
You die.
I think I've tried that wand already.
But just to confirm...
Did I empty this completely?
Not quite.
There we go.
Now it's empty.
I don't know why I'm collecting these luminous drills, but...
I have a feeling, somehow, they could come in real handy.
What is that guy affected by?
Look at that debuff on him.
Worm... is that it?
Oh.
You feel like you're worm food.
Oh!
I see.
Heal me.
Oh god, not these guys.
Get him out of my face.
Can I... drill them?
No.
I cannot, unfortunately, kill my friends.
Toxic rock.
It's actually wild.
It's like the lesser version of...
That feels great, man, doing that.
Oh, but this is a bit of a tricky one, isn't it?
Just a firebolt.
No thanks.
Is this a bad idea?
This is a bad idea.
Don't do it.
Yeah.
That was nothing there for me, anyway.
Uh...
Right.
Your friends.
Your family.
Come with me.
We have enemies to murder.
What the fuck is...
Why is there so much fungus?
Like, what is... oh my god!
This place is raining.
Amazing things down on me.
And I'm all here for it.
That guy is weird.
There was a fireball, of all things.
What else do I have?
I have...
You know what?
The drill could do a lot of damage.
They do ten per, and I shoot a lot of them at the same time.
Never mind.
We're not doing that.
Oh shit, he found the wand!
Okay, at least it's that wand.
It's not that bad.
I'm scared, though.
I have bombs left.
He's still not dead, somehow!
Tell me you're not dead yet!
How?
What's going on there?
What you... what...
Oh my goodness!
Come on, man!
Finally!
Where is he?
Shiny... oh, it's right there.
I don't really want it.
I do want this blood, though.
Now this guy right here is still fucking alive.
It's unreal.
Yes!
Now we can test something critical as well.
Oh no, we don't have water.
Oh yeah!
That is good.
Let's test whether or not this will actually heal me now that the enemy has been using it.
Yes, it will.
I guess that makes sense, because I'm the one with the perk, right?
He doesn't have it.
I do like this one.
Damage plus is insane.
I'm keeping that.
Yep.
It's a good one.
Let's wait for these to go away, because they can damage me.
Come on.
And then I need to dig into this.
Find out what it is.
I could actually use my...
newly found one.
Except, it is a little bit sketchy, isn't it?
Because of the extra damage on it.
Should be fine, I think.
Yeah, let's wait for that and then we teleport in.
Now, what path of dark flame?
Ah, we can heal with it, so...
Hold on, is this dangerous?
Heavy spread?
I am scared.
Actually, the one itself is bad, never mind.
Yeah, that is...
That's some crazy shit right there.
Ah, broken wand!
Not bad.
And then, okay, nice though.
This guy is trapped in there.
I like that, actually.
I want to see what lava has become, man.
I guess we'll figure it out when we kill one of those flying bugs that drip lava.
Wait, what?
Am I done expl...
I'm not done exploring in here.
I see wand there.
I can maybe get there.
Nice!
Watch this.
Whoa!
His projectile hit the thing in front of me.
Insane.
Now, how am I going to get in there?
Ah, I can just do this.
I am kind of scared, though, of hitting myself with these.
What do we got?
A shitty wand.
I can't believe I found so many wands and none of them have been particularly amazing.
Except one.
The damage plus I found was great.
Other than that, not so much.
Look at this guy.
Can't get in here.
Gimme.
Hold on, there's something there.
You there.
Okay, let's see.
Lava?
Oh, no.
No!
It's even worse than lava.
It's the green stuff.
Fuck me.
Oh, well.
It is what it is.
I fucking...
Oh!
Okay, we're fine, we're fine.
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
How the fuck did I just...
Bro, it's everything green!
There we go, there we go.
Yeah, and now it's not needed anymore.
Fuck's sake.
That's not that bad.
I thought we were way lower on HP there.
This was fine, actually.
I totally panicked there.
Oh my god.
I hate the green stuff.
Give me lava.
I want lava!
Anything but the green shit.
Fucking green goop.
Oh, more water.
Give me water.
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
That's the stuff.
And now I want to find just a new one before I move on.
Because I need to heal a little bit.
So, let me do this.
Hell yeah.
Uh, I think I've tried that wand already, but let me confirm.
Oh, wait, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
Ah, teleportation down there.
Oh yes, this one.
Nope,
don't want to go through it yet.
I want to find just one more wand.
How did I...
By the way, just before I somehow teleported through a wall, even though I shouldn't have, it seems like.
Oh, wait, let me use this.
Anything in here?
What's happening in there?
Bro, this is actually digging pretty well.
Phamoxium.
Nah, not interested.
What are those blue ones?
Hold on, can I eat those?
Can we get high in a different way?
That looks intriguing.
Blue fungus.
Wait.
No, no, no, I feel bad.
That makes me sick.
Blue is bad.
Red is good.
Okay, I'm going to try again.
Let's get high.
Can we get rid of the green shit?
Thanks.
We're getting high again.
Oh yeah, eat it all.
That's what I'm talking about.
Holy shit, we're high as fuck, boy.
Oh, toxic sludge echoing and shifting.
Please let it be water.
What is it?
I'm not sure what it became.
But tell me I got rid of the green stuff.
That's all I want.
I'm not sure what it became.
Why do I keep checking this wand like an idiot?
I think I still had one more, this one maybe?
I didn't heal entirely with this.
There's still a little bit.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, yeah, we can heal with this a bit more.
Let's be careful.
That is... scary.
Okay, it's not worth it to heal anymore with that.
I have extracted what I needed.
Switch it back.
And that thing is having a trip.
Similar to me.
Grab more.
Right.
Teleportitis.
Teleport uncontrollably every now and then it says.
So now I want to try and mouse over the next time I have unstable teleportation on me.
Just to see, you know.
Okay, let's go.
This is good.
We don't take this.
Because we can heal later.
Wow, this is looking great.
Let's see the perks.
Melee immunity could be nice.
All seeing eye.
I am kind of tempted to take that.
Just a bit.
But melee immunity, I mean.
I think I may have to take it, man.
I'm taking it.
It's too good.
Let me take this, just in case I get infinite spells.
And that one.
And...
Nuke.
Only a single.
I feel like it wasn't even that good.
Am I crazy?
Summon missile.
Magic missile.
Okay, let's see.
Dude, with the damage plus, we should be able to do something nice.
Let's see here.
And this one does not add damage to me.
So that's a plus.
Adding it to that would already make this one so good.
Well, we can do better than that, I think.
This one reduces recharge time by a lot.
It's because it's called reduce recharge time.
So that makes a lot of sense.
Let me see, what wand is best for this stuff?
Probably this one, right?
That's the best sort of...
No, wait a minute, this one is also pretty damn good.
Cast four spells per.
That's not bad at all.
There we go.
And it's not a shuffle, so it casts four spells.
Let's do...
How about we do a bit of that?
Let's see how good this is.
Let's see the damage numbers.
Oh, but it's super... oh.
Oh, the recharge time is the one that fucks us now, but...
We can do this.
Oh wait, this damage plus isn't affecting... hold on.
If this has spells cast four, I wonder if that means...
I guess I can test that, hold on.
This should do three, six, nine.
Plus three times ten.
So thirty-nine damage?
Thirty-six, wait, what?
Three, six, nine.
Plus...
thirty.
How is that not thirty-nine?
That's weird.
But if I do this...
It's the same.
Okay.
Let me add that.
This is too shit, we need a higher recharge.
Or lower recharge.
What else do I have?
I mean, this one could be nice.
It's a very low cast delay.
Actually insanity, how low that is.
But the recharge time is still kind of high.
Whoops.
But this only casts one spell per, so we should actually do this.
In that case.
Let's see the damage.
Not bad.
Not the worst, for sure.
Ho... homing.
Wait a minute.
This is actually, this is not the near homing.
Is this homing from everywhere I shoot?
Because that could be insane.
Oh my god.
Not bad.
If only we could make this shoot faster then.
Or maybe I just want it on trip.
Oh, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Watch this.
Here, here, here.
Even though this is so fast, maybe I don't need homing on it.
Oh wow, it shoots slower at the beginning.
Look.
And then it homes in.
This is too fast to be effective with the homing, I think.
This one.
Run out of mana super quick.
Does this cost?
Oh, this cost a lot of mana to use.
Oops.
Okay, that's good to know.
That's already cool.
Ah, mana is an issue here.
Yeah, mana is the issue.
I think we may have to go with that one.
That's not bad.
Damage is very decent.
Very respectable.
You know, we could even put this on.
And we're not going to go oomph.
I think I may like that.
I mean, we are going to go oomph, but...
We also go oomph with that.
Nah, let's not have that.
Let's not have that.
I think I like this.
Yeah.
Let me see the other spells.
What was this one?
Large fire bolts.
Electric charge.
Nah.
I don't like any of these.
Unless...
No.
This is my primary damage now.
And then we're still going to have a digger.
So... throw this on here.
We only had two Poland, right?
That's decent.
I like it, but...
Nah, that recharge is too high.
Try on that.
Let's see this.
Honestly, that's better.
Yeah.
Let's just do that.
I like it.
Digging teleport damage.
And that's it.
I'm not going to heal.
We're saving that.
Okay, let's go.
Get the fuck out of here.
So my damage is decent.
If I can find the first one, I can feel more safe.
Dodging freezing vapor.
Oh, that was close.
It's unreal how much better this triplicate bolt is just with the added damage on top.
Because it adds it to all three it shoots.
So it's a huge increase.
I mean, it's not amazing, but it's definitely good.
If only I had concentrated spells right now.
Or a speed up.
Now that would be fire.
I poke my head up, I shoot.
That's the strategy.
Well, that's a machine gun.
Hmm.
I think the best plan is to bum rush it.
No other enemies.
Oh yeah, look where it's standing.
Yeah, wait, you didn't even die from that.
That's wild.
Okay.
I poke my head up, I shoot.
There is something there.
So good.
I need to be closer to the wall.
Oh!
I poke my head up, I almost got shot.
There we go.
Do not hit those pollen.
You know what?
I think I should start using my teleport wand to just dodge projectiles more.
It's so quick to do it.
Like, a projectile comes and you go, what?
You know?
And you have to do the sound effect, of course.
Hell yeah.
Uh oh.
Whoa!
I slipped, I slipped.
I didn't mean to fall down there.
Holy shit, I was oiled up.
That caught me off guard completely.
I was just studying the situation for a second.
And then everything went to crap.
In fact, I kind of want to find a wand here before I get too low on HP.
This is getting dangerous.
This is getting into that territory where it may be stupid for me to continue.
I am being stupid, am I not?
This is dumb, what I'm doing.
Why I do this?
In fact, I suck at long range.
Show me that familiar glow of a new wand, please.
Show me that glistening particle effect.
Anywhere, somewhere.
Uh oh, not that thing.
Sixth strategy, from left to right, left to right, left right, bob and weave.
That goes in my strategy book.
Come on, man.
For all the wands.
Ah, I see one.
Here we go.
What is it?
Energy orb with a timer.
Ooh, nice, and a reduced recharge time on that.
Oh yeah.
And another wand.
My god, the wand sucks though, like...
Let's see this one.
Okay, well, I'm just going to use this to heal.
Cool.
Look at that.
Almost fully healed up.
Lovely stuff.
What was on this wand?
Nothing.
Okay, cool.
We're back in action, baby.
Our fears are over.
This is the... this is a new age.
What a shot!
I applaud you, sir.
That was fantastic.
Top of his sniping class, man.
Of 78.
Famous class, that one.
Really made a lot of good students.
And snipers out of that one.
Oh god.
I poke, I shoot.
Okay, this teleport wand needs to be changed because after one teleport, I'm oom.
That is not good.
It's actually kind of essential that I need to be able to teleport more than once in a short period of time.
Okay, not bad.
Once again.
The game is saving me here.
I just need another wand.
Whoa!
Hello!
I will take your shit.
Will I, though?
No, I won't.
I need my water.
Let's no.
Aha!
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
I am so scared of that.
Let's, uh, hold on.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, it's another one of those!
Uh, sir?
I'm gonna come mess you up, if you don't mind.
Can I...
This dicks, though.
Yes, it does.
Well, sort of.
Whoa, extra max HP as well.
My day is lucky here.
How do I deal with this guy?
I think I just wanna...
...triplicate him.
But he shoots green shit.
Did he just hurt himself?
Oh!
He's dead!
Look at the HP!
Don't shoot at me, you fool!
Shoot the worm!
Get him!
Yes!
Oh, my God.
What is that?
Why is it so big?
Oh!
Oh, wait, I...
Melee immunity!
I forgot about that!
That is incredible!
I feel safe again.
I'm unscared, yo.
To beat this game...
...and cover its secrets...
...and kick this guy's ass...
...and we do it...
...bleep, bleep!
That was the best rhyme I could come up with.
Wait, did I kill the guy?
Wow.
What a wand.
Actually...
No, it's a shitty wand, never mind.
But...
Is it gonna count with the healing?
It is not!
Oh, you're not dead yet, huh?
But I'm immune to your shenanigans!
I still wanna kinda dodge him just in case.
I'm scared.
Holy shit!
Look at all this blood!
I need to kill this guy, because if he angers the gods...
We gotta...
We have to kill him, we have to kill him.
Immediately.
It's a big issue if he angers the gods.
He needs to die.
Yes!
Got it!
Okay.
That's taken care of.
Now we need that wand.
But this guy's protecting it, and he has a little pet with him too.
Hashtag don't like.
What's that?
Nothing.
Fell off?
What is the best way to deal with him?
Maybe to just take it and leave.
Yoink!
In fact, I will throw this on you.
Oh!
That's a lot!
Spells per cast five!
Hey guys!
Oh!
No!
No no no!
Please no!
Have fun!
At least I'm healing with this wand.
Get out of here!
How is he not dead yet?
You know what?
I need a better wand!
I feel like my damaged wand is not quite up to par here.
You know, it's there, but it's not really doing what it needs to do.
Okay, that was that healing.
It's all empty.
Now I need to my other wand back because...
Wait, where's my other wand?
Did it fall down there?
Did that guy pick up my fucking wand?
Sir, that is just not allowed.
In fact, you like that?
Tell me he's dead.
He is dead!
He's dead.
Beautiful.
Thank you!
I will come again.
Taken care of.
Now watch this.
I can kick this in any direction I want.
45 degree angle?
Straight angle?
No problem.
Down angle?
Well, I think at least.
That actually changes so much for me.
Especially the early levels.
Knowing that I can do that.
Like, look at this.
I can get it over this hill.
The double kill.
No, never mind.
It was almost a double kill.
Uh oh.
We've got Ghostbusters in there.
Close one.
Good thing those things don't hit me, huh?
Whoa.
Yep.
What exploded?
Oh, hello!
You know what?
I kind of want that.
To put on a wand wouldn't be too bad.
Digging blast could be cool.
I don't need that because I don't have a plasma beam.
Essence to power could also be really neat.
I'm tempted.
I'm... oh man.
I want all of it.
I think I'm gonna get this one.
Oh, I don't even have enough for another one.
Oh shit, okay.
Let me go collect some money.
I'll be back!
Good sir.
Look at this.
How is that not flipping me off?
You gonna come alive?
Uh oh.
I hate these guys so much.
So what exactly does he do?
He puts teleportation on me when he hits me with that, I think.
And they have so much HP as well.
No wait, he just hits me.
What am I hitting?
Wait, what?
Oh!
Neutralized spells!
Okay.
That explains a lot.
You have been extraordinarily annoying.
Good riddance.
Oh, not this thing.
We gotta take care of the spawner.
Ghostbuster!
How did you hit me there?
Unreal.
Oh!
Fucking... paratrooper there.
Falling from the sky, insta-shooting me.
Give me a wand please.
I'm gonna be saying that a lot.
What's that?
A frozen rat.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
So what does this toxic sludge become?
Is that...
Hello?
This toxic sludge is toxic sludge!
Nothing happened.
Are you kidding me?
It was all a lie.
I was getting high and it was all a lie.
Uh-oh.
Neutralize the threat.
Okay, that works.
85 HP.
We're getting dangerously low here.
Ooh.
This place.
I'm not sure I'm equipped for this.
Actually, hold on, I am.
I am?
No, no, no, I am not.
I was about to say I have all seeing eye, but I don't, because it's not equipped on anything.
Let me just peek and see if there's a wand somewhere.
I don't see anything.
It feels gloomy in here?
Okay, I don't like that.
Gloominess?
No.
Nope.
Not over in low HP.
I don't know what it means, but I don't like it.
Just let me quickly see if there's a wand.
No?
Okay.
Ah-ha!
Wand!
Oh, you're not even dead!
Please die, motherfucker!
God, I hate these things so much!
The worst enemies!
Okay.
Look at that guy guarding it.
Fuck me.
I can't get to that, can I?
No way.
Actually?
Game!
Why'd you do this to me?
I can't actually get it.
Ah!
I'm being sniped now, too.
I see you there.
What?!
I didn't even see your laser!
Bro, that's bullshit.
Fuck this guy.
Hey, hey!
Wanna dance?
Come here.
There we go.
Who's the superior sniper, huh?
It is I!
And I'm about to die.
Come on, man.
One more wand.
Just one for the road.
Y'all good any more than once?
Uno, one-to.
Por favoro.
Show me that glow.
Oh.
I don't like that.
Oh, hell no.
Nope.
We're not doing that.
I gotta admit, I don't remember whether or not we healed in the mountain.
Oh, you're not that dangerous, are you?
What is that?
What's that?
Okay, that's nothing.
Okay.
Thanks.
That was cool.
But I would love some heal instead.
Straight-up heals would be...
Mucho appreciato.
As they definitely don't say in Spain.
Ah, fuck.
There we go.
I don't think I healed in here.
So, let's go.
Oh, let's be careful.
Things could fall on our heads.
Alright.
Yes!
Gaming!
Should I buy anything?
No, wait.
I have 900.
I'm gonna go back to that store I found.
Now, the question is, where the hell was it?
I think it was somewhere down to the left, pretty much.
That's like...
What I remember... Oh, what's that?
Wait a minute.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
What's happening here?
That looks like an eye.
Oh, wait.
This is brickwork.
No, wait.
There's ice?
I have to fill this with something.
Kick it out of here.
Let's try water.
No?
Let's keep an eye out for something nearby.
That will be an indicator, maybe.
I'm thinking about the whiskey one right now.
The annoying thing is, I can't get all the water out of a hole like this.
How do I actually fix that?
You know, that's...
Oh, I can drink it, I guess.
That's it!
That was the solution to that.
What else do I have?
Purifying.
I don't really have many liquids, unfortunately.
I'm not sure I should do it.
What is nearby?
Let's check.
Something about an eye.
All seeing eye.
All seeing eye?
Night vision, aka worm blood?
Hold on.
We have worm blood down here.
I'm gonna get worm blood.
That seems like a logical connection.
It was somewhere down, all the way at the bottom.
Let me kill these guys first.
I swear to God, these guys aim off the charts.
That is electric.
Why is that just there?
Hold on.
Something hidden in here?
My spider senses are tingling.
I still have this.
I kinda want to destroy this thing.
Wait, is it taking any damage?
It is, okay.
Let me go back up.
He had a wand!
Does that count for healing?
Let's test.
Hey, it does!
That's dope.
Okay, so we have a healing wand in here now.
Good to know.
Actually, let me use that.
No, don't use that yet.
What's that?
It's just water.
Let's go back to the eye.
Back to the eye.
What could be nearby?
Oh yeah, I was getting the worm blood.
But wait a minute, let me just check the immediate area.
I could be missing something super obvious, you know?
Uh, I hear electricity.
Ah, it's that guy.
You know what?
Let's kill him.
He will fuck us up later if we don't deal with him.
Also, let me get some water.
There we go.
Oh, he angry.
He angry.
Don't know if I hit him.
Oh no, I didn't.
I got him!
That was clean!
Uh...
Didn't mean to do that.
I didn't mean to teleport into him.
That was a mistake.
Mistake, I tell you.
Shite, sir.
Okay, let me go heal with that wand now.
Better stay topped up at all times.
I see a guy in there.
I see your body.
There's an electric man in there.
Wait, where was this wand?
I think it was here.
Yep.
I use it to dig a little bit anyway.
Nice!
Ah, here we go.
Let me actually just utilize the shot while I'm here.
I think I want...
Hmm...
Digging is already pretty good, I feel like.
We don't need that.
Essence to power could be...
Explosive projectile could also be really nice.
Because that actually adds a lot of damage.
I'm taking that.
That is a lot of damage added.
Okay, now we go up and teach that other electric guy a lesson.
Oh!
I'm tempted to just leave.
This is not good.
Holy crap, he did a lot of damage.
Wow!
What an asshole!
Oh, nice!
Look what I found!
Consolation prize here.
These better... Come on, disappear.
Come on.
Sweet.
I could find another wand.
But, dude, it's...
It's too risky.
I have way too little HP.
Oh, you know what?
This is here right now.
Should I get some?
I should get some, I think.
I just wish I had... You know what?
The purifying stuff seems so rare.
I kind of want to keep it.
Let's try it on this.
Okay, I'm going to empty this and grab the blood.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wand?
I think I already emptied this.
Yes, I did.
I'm tempted to just... go, man.
Hold on.
We can go for a bath.
Wait, why is this already filled with water again?
I must have accidentally done that.
I didn't mean to.
Get rid of it.
I need blood.
Especially because, hey, the worm blood actually puts out fires, too.
So, worst case scenario, I can use it to put out fires on myself.
So, it's actually fine.
There we go.
Don't hit any water now.
Straight down into the blood.
Grab it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yeah, baby.
We are full on it now.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Is someone in here?
Yeah.
Oh!
There's our healing.
Oh, no.
Oh, that seems way too dangerous, bro.
And it's shuffled?
That's not a healing I want to partake in.
I will take the wand, though, because it's sick.
Oh, no.
I'm not using that to heal.
No fucking way.
Nope.
I am an experimenter.
But I'm not that much of an experimenter.
I'm scared of running.
You know what?
I have the blood.
I have to test.
Wait.
It's dark up there.
This is not the place.
Where was it?
Where was the goddamn eye?
I think it was...
I am so... You know what?
I'm so ready to teleport away as soon as I see this fool.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I know where I am.
This way?
Was it left?
Please don't kill me.
Sir?
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Oi.
Come on, man.
It's better work.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Need to empty everything.
There we go.
Wait, does this have...?
Oh, this has some water in it.
There we go.
Pure worm blood.
It's not working.
Hmm.
What the fuck could it be, man?
I need to think on that.
Something shaped like an eye.
What could be in there?
Something about vision.
Also, don't think too hard right now.
Make it to the portal.
And leave.
No, the portal is gone!
Next portal.
This one?
Yes!
There we are.
I'm going, I'm going.
Better play it safe here, and I'm healing.
I'm actually healing.
Yes, sir.
Okay, what do we got?
Bro.
What is with the aiming arcs?
Wait.
Oh, it's almost the same simple.
Look at it.
Another homing.
Tell me I have infinite spells.
Infinite spells.
Aww.
What's that?
Bombs materialized.
Bomb-like spells can be placed in the items space in inventory.
And used like throwable items.
That's actually pretty dope.
Close call.
Uh, no.
Return fire when hit by projectiles.
And you gain 20% resistance against explosions and projectiles.
Okay, but how much return fire?
And what does that mean?
Like how much?
No, I want to re- I want to re-roll.
What?
Oh!
That's where I was just before.
That's where I fought with the guy, remember?
And I threw bombs down here.
Yep.
What do we got?
Someone said a kiwi?
Some kind of minion?
Again, an artifact that allows you to call the celestial rage?
Feared by worms?
Worms run away from you?
I don't care about that because I have melee immunity.
Telepratitis dodge.
You teleport a short distance away.
That sounds terrible.
Fuck no.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
I don't like any of it.
I need to come back and re-roll that shit later.
So, I guess we just move on.
We just go.
Now, let's be careful.
This is the heezy base.
And we don't have a lot of...
I'm an idiot.
I kind of forgot about this.
I should have healed with that.
Or, like, at least modified it so that I can heal with it.
I completely forgot about that.
It happened.
Whoops.
Oh, there's a bomb right at his feet.
That could come in handy.
This is...
the worst!
I don't have anything to fucking kill this guy.
Ugh!
You know what?
Here!
You like warfare so much, why am I stuck?
Goddammit!
Oh, you like that?
There we go, bitch!
So, how do you dead for me?
Whoo!
Hello.
Bait the sniper shot.
Show the helmet.
There he is.
Fuck you.
Eh.
Oh, that's bad.
It's gonna blow!
We are in a terrible spot here.
I'm not gonna lie, this... we have shitty wands.
We're in the heezy base.
But...
we have broken wands.
And that anvil is always sort of to the right.
So, let's stick to the right.
This is gonna be our saving grace.
Hopefully...
we're gonna get something nice.
There's a wand right there.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Oh, fuck this.
Duh!
What?
Uh-oh.
I don't know if I can kill those guys pretty quickly or not.
I don't think I can.
I need this guy to come to me.
Seems like I stun him when I hit him.
Oh, yeah, he totally gets stuck.
Whoa.
I have no damage here.
Long range is really bad for me.
Short range is decent.
It's not great, but decent.
Looky here.
Glowing lands, my beloved!
With firecrackers on it.
You know what?
We have 230 HP.
We can try and shoot this wand and see if we can heal with it.
Let's see how bad this is.
It's gonna shoot it in some direction around me, right?
As long as I'm floating in the air like this, it should be fine.
Yeah!
Okay!
Not bad.
Very nice.
And now we switch it out, I think.
Yeah.
Let's do that.
35 damage, and it has relatively low cast delays, and a bunch of these, so that means fun.
But let's not use it yet.
Only when we've lost some HP.
That guy spawns minions.
Okay, so now we lost some HP.
Let's shoot a glowing lands.
Okay!
I mean, that's the thing.
I just realized, he doesn't spawn all of them at once when he dies.
He spawns them gradually as he takes damage.
I never realized that.
I guess I just always sort of one shot them, so...
What's this?
A reduced spread!
I like that a lot!
In fact, I may take that.
Yep!
Thanks!
And that can even heal us later.
Let's watch this.
Over the bed frame.
Bye-bye!
That was perfectly calculated.
Oh my god.
Come here!
Close quarters?
I'm doing decent damage.
Not the worst.
Not at all.
Actually, this is great.
Whoa!
Here we go.
What's this?
All we need is instant spells now.
And then we're set.
Yo!
I feel like I should take that.
Get rid of this.
But first we gotta heal with it.
So I will come back for that.
Aha!
Wait.
I'll rotate towards foes.
Another reduced spread.
Oh, I'm tempted to just straight up take that.
And then...
Maybe change this back?
What's that?
Infestation.
I think I tried it once?
Not quite sure.
I'm buying it.
We're buying it.
You know what?
I'm gonna actually come back for the infestation thing.
When I have the monies.
This is a dangerous room.
Look at all the explosives.
Should I be healing at all?
Let me heal once with this.
A couple times more.
Just get me the full HP.
Thank you.
Now
the question is the anvil always there?
That is like...
Aha!
You suck!
Amazing!
That's for you!
Come here!
Fuck your bits.
Oh yeah?
How do you like them apples?
Whoa!
What was that shot?
Uh oh.
We've got a mad lad here.
He does something crazy?
Oh he spawns!
Enemies!
That's actually kind of bad for me.
He needs to die.
I like how I say...
That's kind of bad for me.
Of course it's bad for me.
Oh god.
Waaah!
Sick.
Skills.
This guy's having a bath in blood.
Is that one of the wands I tried?
I think it is.
I actually really fucked up not editing my wand.
I could have taken this out up here and everything.
I'm an idiot.
Why did I leave the Holy Mountain so quickly?
I don't understand.
What was I thinking?
God damn it all!
I need peace with gods is what I need.
Let me go back over here.
Oh!
Okay that was a bit scary just now.
I was so lucky.
Uh is this it?
It looks like it.
Oh!
Interesting.
If you put worm blood in here it changes to water.
Isn't that weird?
Ah here we are.
Look.
This is it.
It's always in the bottom right.
Okay moment of truth.
What are we... what's that?
Expanding sphere?
Drilling shot.
Gives the projectile the power to go through the ground?
What?
The wand is not bad either.
That's a great wand.
Hold on.
I thought it would be digging through it but it sort of just phases through and then it starts to do something in the...
That is very interesting.
Let's see the other one.
What do we get?
Weakening curse melee.
Extra melee damage.
Flamethrower.
I don't like these but I do like the wand.
Like the wand in itself is kind of crazy.
Not as good as this one though.
No, I don't want this.
I do want...
this though.
Maybe replace this one.
Yeah.
That seems good to me.
And let's put this here because that's what I'm used to.
How much damage?
75 damage?
Oh that increases damage over time.
What?
Very interesting.
Super slow though.
How fast?
I guess.
So...
Wait, why is this not...
Oh, it's only this one that goes through.
Look at that.
Weird.
Yeah, that does about 70 something damage.
If I can put speed up on that maybe.
And homing, imagine...
I have homing.
Look at that.
Homing.
That would be the day, huh?
In fact.
And another wand.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I need to go back and heal with that wand now.
I may as well use it for that, right?
Let's be smart about things.
So it shoots...
That's actually kind of scary.
Let's do it here.
All right, that heals.
Nice.
Give me that.
And we're out of here.
All I need now is peace with gods and a plasma cutter.
And I can do anything.
How are you not dead?
There we go.
Ah, I'm on fire.
I want to kill this dude.
He's annoying me by existing.
Whoa!
Uh-oh, that was scary.
I almost hit that thing.
Oh, it's right there!
I thought it went to him.
Wait, is it?
Yeah, yeah, it is right there.
Oh, that could have been bad.
That thing does a solid amount of damage.
Look at this.
Wands everywhere.
Like, what's happening?
Damn.
I mean, it's healing.
Sweet.
If I was playing completely optimally here, I would not use that yet.
But when I've taken just a bit more damage.
I'm not that optimal, though.
This is all encased in steel.
Bit of an issue.
Oh!
I wonder if this works with teleport.
That could be an interesting try.
Otherwise, we need the long-distance cast.
Which is super neat as well.
I guess we drain this.
What happened to Toxic Sludge?
Wasn't that changed?
Or not?
Maybe I read that wrong?
What the hell?
Oh my god.
Hello.
Never mind, I'm just walking here.
Wait a minute.
Why is this all brittle glass?
My beloved!
I love that one.
Wait, what did I just take?
Huh?
What did I just pick up?
What the fuck did I just take?
Toxic Sludge to S.T.A.
right.
As if.
Oh wait, Freezing Gaze is a limited...
Oh!
So you need unlimited spells for that.
And what the fuck are the chances that I always found this in the past when I had unlimited spells then?
Because I thought for sure this was just a shoot whenever you want.
You know?
The hell?
Ah, but you know what?
I can heal with it.
So let's do that.
And...
Wow.
Whoa, the game lags when you do that.
What?
Yeah, we're getting rid of that.
Isn't that close blood?
Yeah, that's crazy.
The lag that Wand makes is kind of wild.
Look at that guy.
He is wearing a wand.
Whoa!
Don't you shoot me, sir.
Why is that... I'm stuck.
Oh lordy.
Nice.
That was pretty good.
Another wand.
Man, look at that.
That's all gonna explode.
Oh, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
Watch this.
Wow!
Amazing.
Incredible.
That felt so good.
And the weight slowly just penetrated, you know?
Oh my god, stop.
I'm getting my ass kicked.
Let's not panic, don't panic, don't panic.
Ow!
Guys, calm the fuck down.
Jesus.
What happened there?
It was so strong, it broke through the steel.
Oh shit!
Holy crap!
This guy is healing them!
Are you seeing this?
He's a healer!
Uh oh.
Water, water, water!
This is a dangerous situation.
Holy crap.
I can't loot any of this because of the...
Fuck the fire.
I'm not afraid of fire.
Fuck the fire!
I need money.
I need money for the store!
In fact, let's go.
Uh...
Someone has a black hole at hand.
And that scares me just a tiny amount.
I think he died from it.
He don't play with black holes, man.
It's dangerous stuff!
Oh, it's a guy.
Ooh, see, this is what I'm talking about.
This is when it's worth it.
Now I'm tempted, especially because it heals.
I may even get this...
No, this is such a good one.
I need to keep this one for sure.
Do I love the recharge?
Hold on.
I already have one, don't I?
No, I don't.
Yes, I do.
I don't think I absolutely need another one.
I can go without it, I would say.
Yep.
It shoots two per cast as well.
That's kind of nutty.
What does it do to this guy?
It doesn't actually do anything.
Okay.
Don't shoot me.
Bye-bye.
What's up here?
Oh, are we looping back?
That's actually perfect.
I want to get to the store.
Back to the store.
Ah!
Why do you want to teleport?
What's that little room?
Why is all that?
Let's just fly it from the middle of...
You know what I mean?
Was it up here?
Oh, yeah, here it is.
Here it is.
This one.
That's the one I wanted to try.
Anything else here?
No.
All right, let's move.
I want to go more west now.
So the west we go.
In fact, there was another wand that could heal me somewhere.
That one.
No, wait.
I used...
Did I use all of that on that?
I don't think I did.
There's still some healing left.
Or is there?
I don't...
Wait a minute.
Yeah, this is the lag wand.
Lag me up.
Heal me up.
And I think that's it.
One more.
It doesn't heal one, I don't think.
Yeah.
So when it heals two, that's the end.
Sweet.
Ah, there's the other wand.
What I saw.
A portal there, that's good to know.
We may actually be going through that very soon here.
Dude, I wonder.
So, what if I get hit by the healing?
Will that damage me or heal me?
You know?
That's actually kind of a cool question to ask.
Wait, how do I get up there?
Ah, here we go.
This way?
Ah, that means I forgot I had that.
But that's actually fine.
I wanted to dig anyway.
I was going to use my energy orbs.
Whoa!
Somehow I didn't catch fire, even though it was oiled up.
Completely.
Ah, that guy has a wand.
And what is that he's shooting?
What is that?
Like some kind of crystal.
Can I... I'm scared of you.
Look at this, he's... he's...
Wanding in the left and shotgunning in the right hand.
What a guy.
Oh, you know what?
You know what?
Oh, fuck you, man!
That was glorious.
Oh yeah, it is a crystal.
Phasing arc, it makes a projectile fly much slower, but teleports short distances over its flight.
I failed to see why I would use that.
A crystal that explodes when...
Dude, hold on.
Hear me out.
Dormant crystal?
With explosive projectile.
Hey, hey?
Doesn't that sound cool?
Oh, but this is limited.
Limited item, okay.
Never mind.
You need infinite spells for that, I guess.
But that would be cool.
Do these not explode when I walk on them?
Okay.
So only when...
Let's try it.
Another wand?
Wow.
Fun fact about these guys, it seems that when they shoot their shot, the shot gets shot where they were when they started it, not where they are when they're shot.
Finishes.
If that makes sense.
Okay, watch this.
And a poop.
Let's poop it up.
Heal it up.
Poop, poop, poop, poop, poop.
Wow, you got it.
You want to go and melee with me, huh?
You want to melee me?
What's that?
Unstable teleportation.
Nah.
I don't think I will.
Can I...
How do I dig with this stuff?
It's just snow.
How do I not destroy that with my...
Okay, I do.
It was bouncing off, that's why.
Uh, sir?
Oh!
What?
He spawns those guys?
That's insane.
Wow.
Wait.
Did he replace everyone he spawned every time he shot?
I think that's what happened.
Because I didn't see that many of them.
Just now.
Whoa!
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't burn.
Oh, we're actually right below the holy mount.
Talk about full circle here.
What is that?
What is that thing?
You see...
Oh, it's the trap.
Okay, it just looked very weird for some reason.
Ouch!
That hurt.
There's so much blood here.
I'm running out of black holes.
There we go.
I took a lot of damage there, but I didn't see another way to deal with them.
Oh wait, hold on.
Come on, shoot me.
Shoot me.
Look, he heals them.
Oh, dude, dude.
I have an idea, I have an idea.
Pheromone.
Oh, I killed him.
Oh, wait, I don't have any pheromone anyway.
If I pheromone him...
Imagine.
Is he gonna assist me?
Is he gonna heal me?
That would be crazy.
If I find pheromone, I'm gonna try it.
No!
Nice.
You guys get to live.
I have deemed it so.
I would love to have Tinker with Wands everywhere right now, man.
I feel like I'm leaving so much shit on the table, you know.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay.
Somehow I'm doing really good, and it's only because of the healing with the Wands.
Definitely.
Let's get rid of that explosive.
I could black hole my way in there if I wanted.
Dude, black hole is actually...
If only that was infinite, imagine the digging you could do.
Oh, watch this.
Oh, okay, that's not what I wanted to have it, but okay, all right, all right.
There's a wand there, which means healing.
Which means we gotta get it.
I will make my way in with the black hole.
Boink!
And then we wait for all this to blow over.
Oh my god!
Yep, the whole gang is here.
One at a time.
Ah, it's not that bad.
If they come in one at a time like that, I'm totally fine with it!
Holy Christ.
I'm low on HP.
Sweet.
Get that money.
Let's see what we got.
Ah, easy healing.
Sweet.
Very cool.
Nice.
Another wand!
Lock smiles upon us today.
Where's that quote from?
Acceleration.
Whoop!
Cool if the enemies also get affected by it.
Whoa.
Oh, shit!
That was electrocuted.
Come on, explode, explode!
Wait, he's spawning them!
Insanity!
What a weapon.
This is a fucking sea of flame.
You know what, I'm gonna...
Where's this wand?
Where's this wand I saw?
I'm just gonna black hole my way in, actually.
He has a wand!
Okay.
This looks very much like a wand we saw just before, but it's a little bit different.
Makes any hard, solid materials within a projectile's range turn into sand.
Yo, isn't that kind of nuts?
How is this not ultimate digging?
Oh, it's limited to fuck!
Heal me up!
Look at that!
The digging!
Uh...
Okay, it's only on some of the shots, because it's shovel, I guess.
Yeah, it is.
How is this game completely different every run?
I don't understand.
It's so replayable, it's incredible.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Calm yourself!
I'm not just shooting in that direction, help me.
Whoop!
That is a wand I don't like to see!
Glowing lands, scary.
Three of them, same time, three times as scary.
And then add a little scary on top.
Just for good measure.
Oh, that's...
Ah!
Gah!
Asshole!
I need to surprise this guy.
Oh, oh, you don't know I'm here.
There we go.
Hup!
Let's see here.
25 is an extra damage for explosions, that's not bad.
Let's heal up.
Hey, you like that?
Honestly, when my black holes have run out, I may just replace the wand.
I know I can spell refresh it, but...
eh.
Oh, wait a minute!
If I find a piece with gods, the black holes are my ticket out of here.
Will spell refresh?
That's my home ticket, baby!
I just need to find peace with gods.
Or, I guess, just deal with the gods.
It's also, I guess, a possibility.
I just don't have the very good wands right now.
I don't trust my wands, you know?
To deal with that.
I feel like I need something really badass.
If I were to do that sort of stuff.
What's this?
Acceleration, okay.
Not too bad.
Black hole!
Aha!
Look at this!
I think we should go through.
Why not, right?
Let's go.
Why was that so dark?
For a second there.
Ooh, oh, wow, that's great.
Speed up and add mana on that.
And, wow, another add mana?
What's that?
Brother!
Oh.
Nah, we gotta, we gotta.
Obviously.
Obviously we gotta get that.
There's just no question.
How can you not get that?
Right?
Okay, black holes for now go on the floor.
Go in the corner.
There we go.
Go there.
Now this one.
Hold on.
What do I want?
What should I throw away?
I think these ones can sort of go fuck themselves.
I don't like them.
On this one can also stay here.
All seeing eye could be nice.
To just have on a wand, you know?
I wonder if that gets infinite when you have unlimited spells.
I want to see how fast these expanding spheres are with the speed up.
So if we buy this one.
That's 560.
360.
Ah, 345 is the cheap one as well.
Yes, dude.
Immaculate stuff.
And then this one can go away.
Nobody likes that wand.
Nobody in the entire world enjoys that wand.
A bunch of arrows.
I want this.
That.
Formation.
I mean...
That's kind of cool.
I guess.
Where's my original wand?
Critical and oiled enemies.
Huh.
Imagine if I put a...
So, you know how there's a water modifier?
And...
I think I've seen one other modifier as well.
But if there's an oiled modifier, you could combine that with this.
And it would be kind of cool.
Something I would dig a lot.
Teleport.
We don't need two of them.
Throw one away.
Reduce spread is insane.
Also, we don't want this wand as our teleport wand.
Because of...
The recharge.
No, wait.
Why is that so bad?
Hold on.
Oh, no, wait.
That was our old wand.
This is, this is fine.
This is a fine wand.
Yeah, it's actually pretty good.
Now this one up here.
Now that we have all kinds of crap, we must be able to do some fun.
Already much better.
Speed up.
Much better.
What if we do even more reduce spread?
Oh, I guess it doesn't get reduced much more than that.
It's already quite sick.
Um, ooh.
See, now we're talking.
And that's...
Hold on, how fast is this?
It's kind of slow, isn't it?
How much damage?
Let's test.
45...
45.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, like 45, 60, something like that.
It's still bad.
I gotta be honest here, this...
It's not.
What we need...
Is this, I think.
It's still kind of slow, isn't it?
Also, this is the wand I really want to be using, by the way.
I don't know why I'm using this wand.
It has a shitty recharge time.
Put all this on this one instead.
Wait, why is it doing that?
Modify, modify, modify, modify, modifier.
Ah, it only modifies that one, of course.
That's why.
So, what we need to be doing...
I guess we could double some stuff.
Or...
What, recharge time is 0.27?
How much does... add this?
Man, if we had a chainsaw...
That's what I need right now.
That reduces recharge.
What else reduces recharge?
Ooh, no, this adds recharge.
Wow.
That's a lot.
Holy shit.
Okay, never mind.
That sucks.
Bounces plus 10.
This adds castile.
I guess we could add a homing to it.
Could be cool.
Wow, this adds 0.5 castile?
Damn!
Why is it so... so much?
Hey, that's not bad!
Eh?
I mean, with what we've got?
I guess.
Wait a minute.
Let's see what else we have.
Is there any possibility at all?
Oh, but the good news is, whatever we find out there, we can hot-swap it.
Because we have that perk now.
Let me try this instead.
Still really slow.
Man, I should have brought the other one of this.
I mean, I guess I gotta go with a double.
Remove the homing.
And put on maybe two of these.
How's that look?
Oh, that shoots so slow.
And that's because... why is that so slow, actually?
This reduces recharge time.
This accelerates.
This adds 0.67 cast delay!
But we're not limited by that, because we're using a double.
So cast delay is actually non-issue here.
We're only interested in recharge time.
Unless cast delay is overpowering this right now, and it's simply...
Oh yeah, it is, because look!
The recharge bar never shows up!
So it is indeed.
Cast delay that's dominating right now.
Interesting.
Bounces plus ten.
Spread... oh, wait a minute.
Oh, it's a mod... I thought it was a modifier, but it's not.
Mmm...
Man, I feel like I'm so close to making something great here.
And yet so far...
Maybe I should just go out and explore and find something that can make that the dream, you know?
Maybe just put a homing on it, because...
I mean...
This is just a shotgun, basically, at this point, and it's not super good.
Oh, almost hit that.
Didn't want to hit that.
Like, it's not bad.
The only thing is, the homing could be annoying, because sometimes you want to aim it at a specific point.
So I will actually take that off.
And instead, how about we do this?
No.
Oh, shit.
That's a bad idea.
Well, I don't understand why that's...
Oh, it's weird, I guess, because...
Multicast...
It's multicasting a triplicate, I guess.
And because there's multiple projectiles, maybe it's doing funky stuff.
Funky stuff, indeed.
A?
That's... Why is that so bad?
Wait, I can protect on more...
Oh my god, I thought this was something else.
I thought this was that one thing we had that made an explosion at the impact doing 60-something.
I couldn't understand why we didn't do any damage at all.
This explains it all now.
Fuck me.
That makes more sense.
Okay.
Glad to have that one figured out.
Yeah.
Just run.
That saves it!
We did it!
Mana!
No, not mana.
Because that adds Castile.
Let's reduce it a bit more, can we?
Can we please reduce it?
Just a bit.
This adds...
Okay, okay, okay, that's fine, that's fine.
This is actually totally fine.
We're...
We're back, baby, we're back!
Yeah!
Little fucking Trojan horse.
Where are you?
This one.
This Trojan horse right here.
Fuck off!
You ruined everything for me.
And you know why?
Because I couldn't read, okay?
It's my fault.
Damn it.
Put that there and there.
We have a teleport.
Black hole.
You know what?
Let's do an all-seeing eye on that one.
And then...
I had a bunch of more black holes.
Let me grab those.
And maybe I will...
Let's put this here.
And then let's all...
Oh, dude.
Speed up.
On a black hole.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm scared of trying it in here, but...
Uh...
Hold on.
How bad is this without the speed up?
It's not bad!
I mean, it is bad.
Actually, it is bad.
It's bad.
Never mind.
This is way better.
Yeah, we gotta use it on that.
But I am intrigued by the speed up on the black hole.
Let's grab more of these.
No, come on.
There.
I think I may use a refresh.
I mean, I have so many of them.
Bucket, right?
This one can stay there.
Homing.
What if I put this at the end?
Isn't that interesting how that changes?
This is very interesting.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
What if we double these two together?
Okay.
Well, it was worth a try.
I mean, this is pretty dope.
I mean, I am not going to run out of mana here.
I don't need that mana.
What am I thinking?
God damn it.
Okay.
Grab it.
Look at that shit.
Black holes, ready to engage.
Yes, sir.
And...
That's it.
Let's go.
Whoa!
Wow, we're starting off hardcore here.
Man, I'm so happy I discovered...
the Trojan horse in my wand.
Because I was actually...
Hello.
Are you okay there, sir?
How the fuck did you get in there?
Are you all right?
Can I black hole you?
Come here.
Okay, they still need a bunch of shots for me.
Like, my wand is good, but it's not that good.
It's decent, I would say.
Anyway, dude, I gotta stop it here.
I actually went way over time because I wanted to go to the store, but that's way too late.
Shit.
All right, I guess I gotta scrounge up some food...
somewhere.
But that's it for now.
Dude, this is great.
This is a great one so far.
It's happening.
We're back, baby.
How's everybody, huh?
Let me put on some... atmospherics.
Time to continue my run?
Hey, broke 9999.
Good luck in your run.
Hope it's going well.
How many of you are playing this game?
At the same time.
I mean, not while watching, but like at the same time.
You know what I mean?
That's why I go to the store before gaming.
You know, Lord Eternal?
You're right.
All right, yeah, I have nothing to say to that.
You are right.
I found a...
COV and wand refresh in jungle.
What is that?
I'm not sure what that is.
But that sounds awesome, man.
Keep it up.
Time to continue my run too?
Nice.
Me just a second ago?
I love that you all are playing it.
You're literally playing while watching.
I like that.
Oh, by the way, Wagger, if you're here.
W-H-A-G-G-E-R, Wagger.
Thanks for subscribing with your Prime.
I appreciate it.
And Daftmaff, him is...
resubscribed with Prime.
What's up, man?
Thank you.
Nice stream?
Man, it was great.
I feel like every stream is nice when...
when I'm enjoying myself.
You know, that's when I feel like it's been a good stream.
That's all that matters.
As long as I'm having fun.
Then I feel like that is sort of...
What do you call it?
Not brushing off, but it's like...
When it rains, it pours, right?
So when I'm having fun, it pours down on you and you're also having fun.
If that makes sense.
How many hours now in Neutze?
Let me check.
I can check steam.
Six...
69!
69 hours, baby.
I'm not kidding.
69.5 hours.
Amazing.
WAGGER!
First time... Hey, I see you there.
Thank you, man.
And Dude Mac Miniman.
Just caught up on the VODS yesterday.
Love you to finally catch a stream.
Been enjoying the game as well.
Past few weeks.
It's so fun.
It is, isn't it?
This game is truly something else.
It's so good.
Like...
There are a couple of frustrating moments at times, but...
I feel like those are immediately washed away.
When you start a new run and you have this...
hopeful feeling in yourself.
You know, this time it's going to be different.
I don't know.
It's just so good.
So good.
Nice.
I love that everyone is just in on that.
It's just a cultural thing now.
Everyone knows that one.
Furyforged has eight months in his run.
What?
Hey, Furyforged.
He was the guy who was in the chat the other day.
The Noiteguru, right?
I asked him, are you a Noiteguru?
He's like, I know a couple of things.
And he has eight months in his run.
I feel like he undersold himself a bit there.
He's currently doing a run where he tries to get every material in the entire game in one place.
What the fuck?
That sounds hilarious.
He's a big Noiteguru YouTuber.
Oh, okay.
I see.
So like Dunk or Slam, you guys told me about him as well.
Yes, he's currently streaming his potential thousand hour run right now.
Oh, really?
Damn.
This game is massive, dude.
You know?
I feel like I haven't even scratched the surface, even though I've been playing a lot.
It's wild.
Maybe we should raid him when we're done.
The community is massive as well.
I get that feeling.
I get that similar feeling to Rainworld, you know?
It's a bit of a niche game.
But the fans behind it are so passionate and it's just so cool.
Everyone is sort of enjoying things together and really discovering new things together, you know?
You guys told me there's still secrets in this game.
People haven't discovered yet.
Blows my mind.
Today was a great time, yeah.
Had a couple of funny deaths, though.
The one where I had a wand left behind and I went back to get it and I couldn't find it.
And immediately after, I get killed by that wand.
That is just hilarious to me.
Great moments like that are awesome.
Fury Forest actually played Rainworld today.
Oh, cool.
Did he like it?
If you raid and mine the spoilers.
Oh, when I raid people, I don't watch the stream after.
I just put it on.
Don't worry about that.
Lots of skill issues today.
Are you talking about me or Furyforged in Rainworld?
He's a Rainworld pro?
Aww.
I was kind of hoping he was new to it.
Okay.
I kind of wanted to know how much he struggled.
Damn it.
I'm just trying to get more people to struggle with that game.
So they know how I feel.
Because that game was hard.
Probably the hardest game I've ever played.
Rainworld.
Might actually go back to that one day.
Just to try the new stuff that's coming.
There's a new slug cat coming out.
I'm excited about that.
Did we get a new episode of Prey today?
Oh yes, you do.
Definitely.
I just wanted to wait until the stream was over.
I'm addicted to that playthrough.
Science fiction is the best.
I know, right?
It's so good.
Love that game.
Honestly, I can't get enough of science fiction.
I have run out of good science fiction movies, man.
I've watched them all.
I'm not a big book reader, but I've started reading a lot of books just because I ran out of movies.
And I need sci-fi in my blood.
Oh, you're stocking up on the videos.
That's a strategy, for sure.
Palicado, you don't have to promise anything.
But I definitely suggest playing it first if you're even remotely interested in playing it.
Because it's something of an experience, let me tell you.
Great narrative experience.
And just...
I don't want to say too much, actually.
Yeah, I'm just going to shut up.
What's your favorite sci-fi movie?
Oh!
It's got to be Contact with Jodie Foster.
Maybe followed by...
by Interstellar.
Interstellar was the first movie in my life that I saw twice in the cinema.
I went in again.
I was like, again!
That has never happened to me.
And I always thought people were crazy for going to the cinema twice to watch a movie, but that is the first time.
That was just something else to experience on the big screen.
But Contact...
Contact, guys, if you haven't seen Contact, it's what got me into science.
I shit you're not.
It changed my life.
I wouldn't be here right now, probably, if not for that moment.
Seen Severance?
Technically sci-fi, amazing show.
Is it the one where the cover is a guy with his head sewn off half?
If that's the case, I have not seen it.
But I know of which you talk.
By technically, I mean modern day, but with a specific tech.
Wait, hold on, I need to go back to your last message.
Oh, I see what you mean now.
No, I don't think I've seen that one.
Okay, but I got it right.
It is that one.
Okay, Event Horizon is cool, yes.
Wait, a real good Warhammer 4K prequel?
Okay, maybe we're not talking about the same thing.
On that one.
I'm talking about the sci-fi movie on the spaceship.
I have seen Upgrade Cosmic Whale.
It's super good.
I have watched Westworld Season 1.
It was awesome.
Oh, I watched a lot of shows, Ducky Bird.
I love TV shows.
You know what's funny?
For the longest time, maybe let's say back in 2013 and before that.
I always... I never gave TV shows a chance.
I was a movie guy.
I always thought TV shows would be shit because when you turn on the TV back in the day...
Maybe I'm too old here, but...
But when you turned it on, it was always these shitty shows, you know, like...
I don't know, like these drama shows that were just...
You could just take 10 seconds to look at it and you knew it was shit.
So I just assumed all TV shows were of that quality, you know?
And then my friend one day said, Hey, there's this show called Dexter.
You want to see it?
I'm like, ah, sure.
Okay, let's check it out.
And I watched one episode and I was like, okay, this is...
That was pretty good.
Then we watched one more.
And before you knew it, I blasted through the entire show.
Holy shit.
That was good.
And I was hooked on TV shows after that.
I was converted.
Oh, yeah.
I'm glad I did convert.
You've seen Stargate, right?
Depends which... Are you talking about a movie or the series?
The series?
The original?
I have not seen.
I think I tried to watch it once, but it was kind of late, like a long time after it came out.
And it was a little too dated for me, I think.
It just wasn't that enjoyable for me.
But it's one of those things I want to try again.
Similar to Star Trek.
I haven't watched the original Star Trek show either.
It's great even now.
Maybe we should give it another chance.
Like, so I tried also watching Star Trek the first season.
I'm talking the really old one.
Boys that show old looking.
You know, like I can get over that if like the dialogue and the story and all that is good.
But I don't... It didn't feel like it was, you know?
Do you prefer reading or watching movies?
Watching movies for sure.
Like 100%.
Watching movies you get... You get story, you get visuals, you get audio, you get all of those senses fulfilled.
But there is something to say about reading because you get to imagine the rest, right?
But I've definitely been a movie guy.
Dude, slightly dated.
Children of Men is completely not dated.
It is still incredible today.
Such an incredible movie.
But I agree.
You should watch it.
It's a joy.
Stargate 1, Stargate Atlantis are pretty good.
I think I will give Stargate another chance one day.
Maybe together with a friend.
Did you watch Primer?
I did.
I didn't enjoy it very much though.
I think it was needlessly complicated and...
I didn't think the acting was... The acting was not good at all.
I didn't like... I didn't enjoy that.
Dude, we can talk about movies forever.
I fucking have seen so many movies.
I love movies.
That would be fun to have like a discussion about that someday.
Like in more detail.
Just talking about movies, shooting the shit.
The Road with Viggo Mortensen?
Yes.
That one slaps.
Great one.
Arrival was cool too.
Yeah.
I like that one.
Look at us nerds.
The Expanse is a great sci-fi show.
It is.
Oh, you've heard it, but it is.
I can tell you that.
I've seen it.
It's good.
It's not perfect, but it definitely scratches that sci-fi itch.
Have you watched the ritual?
Hold on.
Maybe.
2017.
I can see the link is purple for me, so I've clicked on this before.
A group of college friends reunite for a trip to a most dangerous country in Europe.
Sweet!
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I think one of you suggested this before as a joke.
I remember reading this out loud before on stream.
Am I tripping right now?
I feel like I read that out loud and I laughed too, because it sounded so absurd at first.
You know?
I have not seen that movie.
Yeah, you are the one hive.
Okay, I'm not crazy.
You love that movie?
Okay, I really gotta watch it then.
In fact, I have it on my list.
I added it back then.
So on IMDB, you can have a watch list.
I added it to that.
Cabin in the Woods is fucking great!
The humor and the jokes in that is some of the funniest stuff I've ever seen.
Without revealing too much, the first half, or like one first third of that movie is the most fun shit I've ever seen.
First time I watched that, man.
I was dying.
The acting, especially those actors.
The guy who plays Joshua Lyman in the West Wing has a character in that movie, and it's just, he's so funny.
What's his name?
Bradley Whitford.
I have seen Annihilation, it was okay.
The Prestige is also amazing.
Classic Nolan movie there.
So many good men.
Am I getting old?
I started to have this feeling now.
Man, movies are just not being made at the same rate.
I mean, good movies are not being made at the same rate that it once was.
Seem Drog, of course!
I'm actually not the biggest fan on Danish movies, but that one was really good.
Actually, hold on there, there is a bunch of good Danish movies.
The Hunt, also with Mass Megalsen, is fantastic.
12 Angry Men, unbelievably good movie.
I've shown that to so many people.
They're always so apprehensive about it because it's in black and white, but it's honestly one of the least dated films to ever exist.
Even today, it's incredible.
Because the acting is just so good.
Let's run the topic of shows, how about some anime?
So I haven't watched almost any anime in my life.
When I was in the US, last year, I think October-ish, it was during the Zelda playthrough, Breath of the Wild.
I watched some of... what is it called?
Titan something.
The Titans, I think?
Something like that.
And it was actually okay, you know?
But then I sort of... I stopped watching it and then I didn't get back into it.
Revenge of the Titans, I think, or something.
Attack on Titan, thank you.
Yes.
Attack on Titan.
I saw some of that and it was actually okay.
You knew I was going to say that?
Oh, okay.
I think I talked about that on the Discord back then.
What is JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?
Is that an anime?
Almost like a kid's show.
Oh yeah, it is an anime.
I've got to be honest, I'm not the biggest fan of animation in general as a film thing.
And it's only because there are no real characters like humans acting.
One of the things I enjoy most about movies is seeing the acting and the small micro acting in people's faces.
That means so much to me and all that is lost when you do animation.
So I used to love them way more as a kid, but not anymore so much.
And it's only because of that.
It's just something I really enjoy in movies.
And I also just... the whole, like, okay, here's a really nerdy thing, okay?
But in some movies, one of my favorite movies ever is Black Swan, okay?
And there are certain times in that movie where the shot itself that is there, like with the camera placement, and there's a certain transition in that movie, whenever I watch that I get the biggest movie bone error.
I get chills down my back just because of how good that is.
And you can't get that in the same way in animation for me.
Here's another example.
In Lord of the Rings, I think the third movie.
I'm gonna spoil it, okay, real quick here.
If you haven't seen it, just spoil it there.
But there is a shot at some point where you have, I forget the name of the city, but this huge city on the mountainside in the distance, right?
And the shot is following a horse.
It's Gandalf.
He's riding.
There's no music.
It's just the hooves, no?
And the shot is behind, it's following, and it's sort of shaking, right?
And while that's happening, it sort of pans over to the right with the city in the distance.
The sequence is so fucking good!
Oh, just thinking about it right now makes me go crazy.
You know, those are the things I enjoy so much in movies, and yeah.
I love that stuff, man.
I love it.
Black Swan is, for me, it's the perfect movie.
Like all the way through.
It's the only movie I've ever seen where I wouldn't change a single thing.
It's insane.
I've seen the menu.
It's great.
Yeah.
I saw it with my friend, Peter.
Arcane?
You know what?
Okay, Ducky, I gotta tell you this.
I watched Arcane, actually, and I was really impressed.
I enjoyed my time so much with that.
That's one of the very few animation... or like, animes, you could call it, I guess?
That I enjoyed a lot.
I also really like that one movie with the rat.
Ratatouille.
That is a good movie.
Honestly, I think I need to give more... more animes a chance, basically.
Because there are some good ones out there, for sure.
And I'm just an old man sitting here, you know?
Season 2 comes in November?
A-hype.
I'm looking forward to that.
I may actually watch the first season again, just because it was that good.
Arcane is incredible, and that's coming from someone who doesn't enjoy stuff like that a lot, so...
A friend of mine is begging me to watch it.
You have a good friend.
Have you seen everything everywhere, all at once?
I have.
I... I gotta be honest.
It wasn't my thing.
I watched it with a couple friends.
And I watched it all the way through, but if it wasn't for them and I wasn't alone, I would have probably switched it off halfway through.
I was just bored, man.
It wasn't for me.
But the... what do you call it?
The concept behind it was really cool.
The idea behind it.
The Truman Show?
Of course!
What kind of question is that, man?
I've been quoting the Truman Show.
Good afternoon, good evening, good night.
Come on!
Okay, you know what?
I need to scrounge up some food in my kitchen.
I'm dying.
I gotta eat.
Guys, thank you so much for watching.
Let's try and rate the...
What was his name?
Fury.
You said he's streaming right now, right?
Why not?
Let's go for it.
Oh, same category?
Oh, okay.
Okay, yeah, let's do it.
Here we go.
Have fun, guys.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you in the next stream slash video.
Bye-bye.